‪接着上次讲到的地方
Considering where we left off,
‪我想你该会有一些问题
I'm guessing you might have a few questions.
‪从我跟诺亚表白后
Well, from the moment I told Noah...
‪我爱你
I love you.
‪直到他最终离开
Till the moment when he finally left,
‪发生了很多事情
a whole lot of stuff happened.
‪让我告诉你最新情况
Let me bring you up to speed...
‪学校一放假‪弗林家的海滨别墅就开放了
As soon as school ended, the Flynns opened up their beach house.
‪ -诺亚和我在那里过了整个夏天‪ -天啊
Noah and I spent the whole summer there.Oh, my gosh!
‪收到了一份很棒的礼物
Got an awesome gift...
‪玩桌游到凌晨3点
Played board games till three in the morning.
‪放烟花 这次是在沙滩上
Made sparks fly. This time on the beach.
‪跟老朋友打招呼
‪看到了美丽的日落
Said hi to an old friend, watched a gorgeous sunset...
‪看着诺亚入睡
Watched Noah sleep,
‪看着诺亚学玩轮滑
watched Noah try to rollerblade,
‪用我最喜欢的方式看日出
watched the sun come up in my favorite way,
‪然后 就这样
and then, just like that,
‪27天前 我的心飞走了
exactly 27 days ago, my heart flew away.
‪诺亚走后 一切都很艰难
After Noah left, it was hard.
‪他说想尝试异地恋
He said he wanted to make long-distance work,
‪但我决定成熟点‪让诺亚有自己的空间
but I decided to be a grown-up about things and to give Noah his space.
‪我想这是那种高年级学生的成熟
I guess that's the kind of maturity that comes from being a senior.
‪换句话说 我没事
In other words, I was okay.
‪同时 我会尽量不去想
Meanwhile, I did everything I could to keep my mind off the fact.
‪诺亚远在5000公里以外的事实
That Noah was 3,000 miles away.
‪我开始写申请大学的个人论文
Like I started working on my college essay,
‪开始和李尔一起做电子游戏播客
started a podcast about video games with Lee.
‪ -游戏开始‪ -已经有一批订阅用户
- Game On! - Already got subscribers,
‪非常感谢
- thank you very much. - Foreign Danger!
‪终于在XBOX上战胜了对手
And finally dominated my nemesis on Xbox...
‪在海滨别墅看终极飞盘赛
Watched Ultimate Frisbee at the beach house,
‪跟李尔、瑞秋一起看八十年代的电影
watched '80s movies with Lee and Rachel,
‪看着李尔坠入爱河
watched Lee fall completely in love,
‪看着李尔有了超级健美的身材
-watched Lee get a super buff bod, -Ooh!
‪看着女孩们欣赏李尔的健美身材
Watched girls watching Lee's super buff bod,
‪申请护照 申请信用卡
applied for a passport, applied for a credit card,
‪甚至和李尔一起‪申请了我们梦想中的大学
even applied with Lee to our dream college.
‪第19条规矩 一定要和你的好友同校
RULE NUMBER 19: Always go to the same school as your bestie.
‪对我们来说 说到大学
And for us, when it comes to college,
‪就是指加州大学伯克利分校
that means the University of California at Berkeley.
‪加州大学伯克利分校
UC Berkeley is this totally dope,
‪是加州北部最无与伦比的学校
completely amazing school in Northern California.
‪自从发现我们的母亲
Lee and I have dreamed of going there
‪在那里成为闺蜜后‪李尔和我一直梦想读这所学校
ever since we found out that's where our moms became besties.
‪那里有很酷的钟楼‪还有祈求好运的山头翻滚
It has a really cool tower, hill rolling for good luck,
‪著名的照片墙松鼠 还有表情包页面
famous Insta squirrels, and a cool meme page.
‪这是为了你 妈妈
This one's for you, Mom.
‪带布拉德去玩街机‪带李尔和瑞秋去徒步
Took Brad to the arcade, took Lee and Rachel hiking,
‪为诺亚拍了张坏坏的照片
took a naughty photo for Noah,
‪但却不敢发
chickened out about sending it though.
‪最后一件事是‪我留给自己的独处时间
And the last thing I took was one final moment all to myself.
‪到夏天结束时
By the end of the summer,
‪我觉得和诺亚的事情解决了
I was feeling pretty sorted out about things with Noah.
‪他在他该在的地方 我在该在的地方
He was where he was supposed to be, and I was where I was supposed to be.
‪如果这样也能行 很好
And if it works out for us, great!
‪如果不能 也没关系
But if not, that would be okay too.
‪像我说的 我很好
Like I said, I was okay...
‪大部分时候
mostly.
‪我在为第一天上学做准备
And here I am getting ready for my first day of school,
‪一切似乎有点不同
and everything seems... different somehow.
‪她来了
There she is.
‪最后的第一天 我走了
Last first day! I gotta go.
‪爱你
Mmm! Love you. Love you.
‪ -更爱你‪ -好了 我要…
- Love you more. - All right, I'm gonna...
‪ -嗨‪ -好吗？
What up?What up?
‪噢 这是什么？
Oh, what is this?
‪打开吧
Open it.
‪好的
Okay!
‪很有趣
Very funny.
‪噢 我能说什么？
Oh, what can I say?
‪我想你可能需要后备的后备
I thought you might need a pair of those back-up back-ups this time.
‪你还是该穿一下 会看起来很瘦
You should try those on, though. I think they would look quite slimming.
‪嘿 你去哪里？学校在那边
Hey, uh... where are you... Where are you going? School's that way.
‪去接瑞秋
Going to get Rachel.
‪明白
Oh. Gotcha.
‪你好吗？小妖精
What's up, foxy lady?
‪对 好像
Yeah, right. As if.
‪噢 好的
Oh, okay.
‪来吧 各位
Let's do it, y'all.
‪什么？
What?
‪我在想我有多幸运
I'm just thinking about how insanely lucky I am.
‪好了 小情人 我们走吧
All right, lovebirds.
‪高三
Let's go! Senior year!
‪嘿
Hey!
‪发生什么事？
‪我不知道
- What is going on? - I have no idea...
‪我对高年级感觉非常好
I had been feeling pretty damn good about senior year.
‪直到所有人望着我‪好像我的狗死了一样
That is until everybody was looking at me.
‪ -嘿 艾莉‪ -嘿 塔宾
- Hey, Elle. - Hey, Tuppen.
‪听说你和诺亚分手了 我真的…
Just heard about you and Noah breaking up.
‪没有 我们没有分手
- I was really hoping... - No, we didn't break up.
‪抱歉 我觉得你们很配
I'm sorry. I thought you guys were really great together.
‪ -我只是…‪ -不是…我们没有…
- I just... - That's not... We didn't... um...
‪ -是你的决定还是他的‪ -算了
- Was it your decision or his? - Never mind.
‪有时我讨厌高中
Ugh! Sometimes I hate high school.
‪早上好 欢迎回来 洛杉矶乡村日
Good morning and welcome back, Los Angeles Country Day.
‪希望你们度过了美好的暑假
We hope you all had the very best of summers
‪准备好开始另一个精彩的学年
and are ready for another outstanding school year.
‪任何社团想向学生会‪汇报秋季筹款活动创意
Any clubs wanting to present fall fundraiser ideas to student council
‪必须在今天下午3点进行 我们忘了亲吻亭的汇报
- must do so today at three p.m. sharp. - We forgot about the presentation for the kissing booth!
‪ -噢 天啊‪ -快点去做
- Oh, my God. - Get busy!
‪我们今天的名言是
And our quote of the day:
‪“生命中最棒的 就是彼此相守”
"The best thing to hold on to in life is each other."
‪经典电影明星奥黛丽·赫本的佳句
Beautiful words from an iconic film star, Audrey Hepburn.
‪说得好 奥黛丽 说得好
Well said, Audrey. Well said.
‪祝大家今天愉快
Have a fantastic day.
‪好了 各位
All right, everyone,
‪我们拿出暑假的阅读材料
let's all take out our summer reading material.
‪太棒了 我很惊讶
That was so good. I was so surprised.
‪（格温内 米娅 奥丽薇拉）
‪（要你命女孩）
‪噢 来了
Oh, and here we go.
‪天啊 艾莉 你还好吗？
Oh, my God, Ellen, how are you?
‪哈佛有很多漂亮的女孩
So many beautiful girls at Harvard.
‪ -有经验的女孩‪ -异地恋是很难的
- Experienced girls. - And long distance is tough.
‪完全解释了为什么你们‪没有新的社交动态
Totally explains why you guys aren't posting on social anymore.
‪噢 诺亚和我决定在社交媒体上‪保持低调
Oh, actually Noah and I decided to keep it low-key on social,
‪这样就不会有压力
so we wouldn't feel pressured by it.
‪太聪明了 分手是很残酷的
That is so smart. Breakups are brutal.
‪太残酷了
So brutal.
‪我们并没有分手
We didn't break up, though.
‪邮政编码都不同‪分手基本是自动发生的事
With different zip codes, breakups are basically automatic.
‪ -自动的‪ -好了 我们走
- Automatic. - Oh, well. Gotta go.
‪我想去看看新转学过来的帅哥
I wanna take a peek at the new snack that just transferred in.
‪在教室看到他了 他叫马可‪真的很性感
Saw him in homeroom. His name's Marco, and he is seriously luscious.
‪你和弗林真可惜
Ooh! I'm sorry about you and Flynn.
‪好的
Um, okay.
‪谢谢 再见
Thanks. Bye.
‪（你在吗？）
‪抱歉打扰了
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
‪艾莉·依云丝 办公室有你的电话
Elle Evans, there's a phone call for you in the office.
‪是你爸爸
It's your father.
‪他说有急事
He said it's urgent.
‪ -电话在那边 亲爱的‪ -好的
- The phone's over there, honey. - Okay.
‪ -天 希望不是很严重的事‪ -喂？
- Gosh. I hope it's nothing too serious. - Hello?
‪你怎么回事？
What's going on with you?
‪什么？
What? Uh...
‪什么意思 爸爸？
What do you mean, Dad?
‪为什么不回我短信？
Why aren't you texting me back?
‪什么？
Well... what?
‪噢 天啊 你说的阿姨的事太可怕了
Um... oh, my God!
‪罗斯
Rose.
‪没事吧？
Is everything okay?
‪ -能给我点私人空间吗？‪ -好的
- Could I please have a moment in private? - Sure.
‪等我一下 我要走进办公室
Just give me a second.
‪花点时间来平复心情
I'm stepping into the office to take a second to process this.
‪你为什么要扮作是我爸爸？
Why are you pretending to be my dad?
‪只有这样才能让你接电话
It was the only way I could think to get you on the phone.
‪噢 不是这样的
Oh, that is not true.
‪就是这样 你很少打电话‪就算你发短信
No, it is true. You barely call, and when you text,
‪你会发些奇怪的两个字短信
you send these weird two-word text messages
‪比如 “保重” “后聊”
like, you know, "Take care," "Talk soon."
‪你是要跟我分手？
Are you breaking up with me?
‪什么？不是 完全相反
What? No, no, no, no! The opposite.
‪然后呢？为什么？你为什么不理我？
Then what? Why? Why are you ignoring me?
‪我…我不知道 我…
I... I don't know, I...
‪我想我只是…
I guess I'm just...
‪我想表现得成熟点‪不要像个粘人的女朋友
I'm trying to be mature and not come off like some clingy girlfriend.
‪艾莉 我跟你说过 我想继续这段关系
Elle, I told you that I wanted to make this work.
‪我知道 但人们离开的时候‪总是会这样说
I know, but people always say that when they leave.
‪我只是想给你空间
I just wanted to give you space
‪让你想清楚 你是否真的要这样做
so that you could figure out if this is really what you want.
‪空间 我不想要空间
Space. Space. I don't... I don't want space.
‪空间不是我想要的 我告诉你
Space is not what I want, I told you.
‪我不想要空间 我想要你
I don't want space. I want you.
‪我希望你一直在我身边
I want you around me all the time.
‪我现在就想要你在我身边
I want you with me right now, actually.
‪我只想要你 好吗？
I just... I just want you, okay?
‪发短信给我
‪打电话给我
Text me, call me,
‪给我飞鸽传书 什么都行 好吗？
send me a messenger pigeon, whatever it is, okay?
‪不管怎样 只是别给我空间 好吗？
Whatever it is, just don't give me space, okay?
‪好的
Okay.
‪首先是艾莉·依云丝和李尔·弗林
First up are Elle Evans and Lee Flynn.
‪大家好 我们对今年筹款活动
Hello, everyone. Um, we are excited about this year's fundraiser
‪和我们面前的机会感到兴奋
and the opportunity before us.
‪基于去年的收入 我们认为…
Based on the earnings from last year, we believe that it would be beneficial...
‪大家都同意让舞蹈社‪再为筹款活动做亲吻亭
Everybody in favor of Dance Club doing a kissing booth again for the fundraiser,
‪ -同意的请说“同意”‪ -同意
- please signify by saying "Aye." - Aye.
‪ -同意‪ -反对的请说“反对”
- Aye. - All those against, say "Nay."
‪反对
Nay.
‪等等 不是 我不知道为什么这样说
Wait, no, I don't actually know why I just said that.
‪我们将记录获同意通过
Let the record show the Ayes have it.
‪亲吻亭得到批准
The kissing booth is approved.
‪现在已经有结论了‪但我们真正好奇的是
And now that that's settled, what we're all actually curious about is
‪这次你们选择的献吻者都有谁
who you've selected for the lineup of kissers this time.
‪因为没有弗林负责招揽生意
Because without Flynn as a headliner to draw in business,
‪今年的展台可能不够吸引
the booth may not do so well this year.
‪ -说得有道理‪ -去年将很难超越
- Uh, that's a good point. - Last year is gonna be hard to top.
‪ -我们…‪ -太难了
- We... - So hard.
‪确实 有想法吗？
Quite true. Thoughts?
‪事实上 我们的想法是
Well, actually, the thoughts we're having...
‪对 有道理 很好
Right. Right. That's a good point. Great point.
‪我们决定对今年的名单保密 对
Well, you know, we have decided to keep this year's list a secret. Yeah.
‪但不用担心‪我知道你们心目中的对象
But do not worry because I know who a lot of you are already thinking of,
‪答案是肯定的
and the answer is yes.
‪他们会到场
They will be there.
‪噢 宝贝
Whoo! Thank you!
‪所以 我们还没找人 对吧？
So, we didn't actually get anyone yet, did we?
‪ -完全正确‪ -好吧
- That is correct, yes. - Okay.
‪ -罗斯阿姨怎样？‪ -噢 别这样
- So how's Aunt Rose? - Oh, come on.
‪你别再傻笑了
You can stop smirking now.
‪我想你 坏蛋
I miss you, jerk.
‪我更想你
I miss you more.
‪你在学校已经出名了吗？
So, you Big Man on Campus yet?
‪没有 不是这样
No, not exactly.
‪这边有点不同
It's kinda different here.
‪你什么意思？
What do you mean?
‪嗯
Well, uh...
‪怎么了？
What's wrong?
‪没有 没什么事 只是…没关系
Nothing! No, nothing's wrong. Just... doesn't matter.
‪嘿 想家是正常的
Hey, it's okay to be homesick.
‪我很好 真的 我很好 只是…
I'm... I'm fine. I'm... seriously, I'm fine. It's just, you know...
‪你呢？你怎么样？‪有申请更多学校吗？
What about you? How about you? Have you applied to any more schools?
‪别跟我提伯克利
Don't even get me started on Berkeley!
‪如果李尔和我都进不去 我…
If Lee and I both don't get in, I'm...
‪别告诉我 你只申请了一家学校 艾莉
Don't tell me you've only applied to one school, Elle.
‪我知道
I know,
‪但这确实是唯一我们说过想去的学校
but it's literally the only school we've ever talked about going to.
‪嗯
Well...
‪你知道你能做什么吗？
you know what you could do?
‪ -天啊 他是要叫我…‪ -申请这里
- My God. Is he about to ask me to... - Apply here.
‪你说得好像我能进哈佛一样
As if I could get into Harvard.
‪艾莉 波士顿有超过30家学校‪你可以申请
Elle, there's over 30 schools that you could apply to in Boston.
‪你意思是 至少有一家会接受‪可怜的我？
And your point being that at least one of them would accept my sorry ass?
‪不是 我是说 如果你去不了伯克利
No! My point being that if you don't get into Berkeley...
‪也许你可以考虑来这边的学校
maybe you can come to school here.
‪跟我一起
With me.
‪我想要这样
I'd like that.
‪你虽然看不到‪但我的心就像做了后空翻
You obviously couldn't see this, but my heart just did a backflip.
‪好的 也许我会考虑的
Okay, yeah, maybe I'll think about that.
‪也许你要考虑一下
Maybe you'll think about it.
‪好的 你可以考虑
Okay, you can just think about it.
‪如果你来这里…
You know, all the books you have to read if you go here, seriously...
‪（嘿 好吗？）
‪我不禁想起了第19条规矩
I couldn't help but think about rule number 19,
‪但现在的情况
but here's the thing.
‪谁知道我能不能‪被波士顿的学校录取？
Who knows if I'd even get accepted into a Boston school?
‪如果我没被录取
And if I didn't,
‪没发生的事现在告诉李尔 让他不开心 这有什么意义？
what would be the point in telling Lee now and getting him upset over nothing?
‪对吧？
Right?
‪你的成绩很好
You have excellent grades,
‪优秀的学业成绩 足球 舞蹈社
great test scores, soccer, Dance Club.
‪我还有一个电子游戏播客
And I also have a podcast about video games.
‪噢 那你很有影响力？
Oh! So you're an influencer.
‪有多少个订阅用户？
How many subscribers?
‪37个
Thirty-seven.
‪37万个
Thirty-seven thousand!
‪ -我们可以利用‪ -不是
- We can work with that. - No, no, no, um...
‪37个
Thirty-seven.
‪你在开玩笑 对吗？
You're kidding, right?
‪嗯
Oh. Well, uh...
‪要进入加大伯克利和哈佛‪这样的顶级大学
To get into top-tier colleges like UC Berkeley and Harvard,
‪你真的要用你的个人论文‪来打动他们
you really need to wow them with your personal essay.
‪但你的论文…
And yours is...
‪我该怎么说？
How shall I put this?
‪ -真的吗？我以为写得很好‪ -嗯？什么？不是
- Really? I thought I killed it. - Hmm? What? No.
‪你甚至没到合格水平
You didn't even wound it.
‪那么 我要重写个人论文
So, I'm redoing my personal essay.
‪显然它很烂
Apparently it sucks.
‪噢 新记录
Oh! New level!
‪不知道我的是不是很烂‪我应该了解一下
Wonder if mine sucks. I should probably look into that.
‪不能让这个阻碍我们申请伯克利
Don't want that keeping us out of Berkeley.
‪是的 当然
Um, yeah. Definitely.
‪你见过新来的马可吗？
So, have you seen the new kid Marco yet?
‪是的 帅得无与伦比
Yeah. Devastatingly handsome.
‪有人说他比诺亚更性感
Some are even saying he's hotter than Noah.
‪ -真的吗？什么？‪ -是的
- Really? What? - Yeah.
‪那太疯狂了
That's crazy!
‪噢 李尔 新记录 李尔
Oh, Lee! New level, Lee!
‪李尔？不 李尔
Lee? Lee! No! Lee!
‪我们说过的 我玩吃豆人游戏时
We discussed this. I need a regular feeding regimen
‪我的手没空 需要你定时投喂
during my hands-free Ms. Pac-Man experience.
‪那是什么鬼？
What the hell is that?
‪最高分是MVP？
Top score is "MVP"?
‪最有价值玩家？嗯 有些人自视甚高
"Most Valuable Player"? Well, somebody thinks highly of themselves.
‪我一直以为我们会永远第一
I kind of always just figured we'd be number one forever.
‪看着我
Look at me.
‪我们需要冰沙 油条和一大堆硬币
We are going to need slushies, churros and an ass-load of quarters.
‪惊喜
Surprise!
‪（生日快乐 马克校长）
‪嘿 依云丝
‪过来
Hey, Evans. Come here.
‪怎么了？
What's up?
‪那个新来的马可‪有人偷拍他健身的视频
That new guy Marco, someone snagged a video of him working out.
‪噢 不是吧
Oh, come on.
‪这家伙究竟有多性感？
How hot can this guy actually be?
‪他不可能那么性感
He can't be that hot.
‪性感
Hot.
‪他只是个男生 哇 老天
He's just a guy... whoa! Sweet mercy!
‪天啊 不是吧
Jeez! Hello!
‪天啊 要你命女孩说得对
God! The OMGs were right!
‪这家伙确实是零食
This guy is a snack indeed!
‪可能还是主菜
‪可能还是甜品
Maybe an entrée! Maybe he's also the dessert too!
‪再多说一点
Tell me more!
‪不行
No, no, no.
‪也许他是餐后甜品‪这是我们正在吃的大餐
Maybe he's the after-after dessert! He's a big meal that we're having now!
‪噢 该死 对不起
Oh, shit! Sorry.
‪很抱歉
- Oh!! - Sorry about that. Whoa! Oh!
‪他能同时举起你和我
He could bench you, us together at the same time!
‪是 当然
Yeah, definitely.
是的 是的 你想要一些这个...
Yeah, yeah, Do you want some of this...
‪我很困惑 我是否需要眼镜？
I'm confused. Do I need glasses?
‪眼前的是一盘冰块还是六块装的？
Am I looking at a tray of ice cubes or a six-pack?
‪ -我说得对吗？真是难以置信‪ -该死
- Am I right? It's incredible! - Shit!
‪就像他的汗会发光一样
It's like his sweat produces its own glitter!
是的 是的 我可以得到一个是的
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Can I get a yeah...
‪我们能买两张枪展的票吗？
Hello, can we get two tickets to the gun show, please?
‪因为那是手臂还是大炮？
Because are those arms or cannons?
‪噢 我的天
Oh, my God!
‪这不好玩 各位
- It's not funny, everybody! - Whoa!
你想要这个吗...
Do you want some of this...
‪如果这些腹肌发在照片墙
If those abs had Instagram,
‪ -估计马上有百万粉丝‪ -哇
- one million followers all day! - Wow!
‪我不算迷恋屁股那种人
I'm not really a butt person,
‪但我现在能理解他们
but, like, now I understand people who are!
‪我不知道是要舔 拍 还是咬
I don't know whether to lick it, smack it, bite it...
‪ -咬？‪ -这三样我都想做
- Bite it? Ugh! - I wanna do all three of those things.
‪兄弟 很抱歉
Dude, I'm so sorry.
‪就叫我地震姐吧
‪因为我现在真的全身在震
Just call me an earthquake, because I am legit shook right now!
‪噢 哇
Whoa!
‪再说一次他的名字？
What is his name again?
‪马可
Marco!
Marco! Marco! Marco! Marco!
‪ -马可‪ -马可
- Marco. - Marco.
‪李尔？
Lee?
是是是 我得到了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I got it
‪天啊
Oh, my God!
‪这事我可以笑一年
Oh, that made my year.
‪你真是精彩
You're cool.
‪你好 依云丝小姐
Hello, Miss Evans.
‪生日快乐
Happy birthday!
‪嘿 看 是那个“很懂”的女孩
Hey, look, it's the "get it" girl.
‪宝贝
Baby, baby!
‪天啊
Gosh!
‪我想大家明天就忘记了
I bet everybody forgets by tomorrow.
‪没关系
Well, that doesn't matter
‪因为我要转学到月亮上的学校
because I'm still transferring to a school on the moon.
‪他真的有那么帅吗？
Is he really that good-looking?
‪抱歉 是我的描述不够生动吗？
I'm sorry. Was my description not vivid enough?
‪我基本上是用了100种方式‪来形容马可
I literally described a hundred different ways Marco can get it!
‪太棒了
Awesome.
‪我想你是广播里那个人吧？
I take it you're the one from the intercom?
‪是的
Mm-hmm, yeah.
‪你知道 他们已经叫我“很懂”女孩‪但我叫艾莉
But they're, you know, already calling me the Get it Girl, but I go by Elle.
‪我不知道 “很懂”女孩听起来不错
I don't know. Get it Girl has a nice ring to it.
‪好吧
Cool.
‪那是你的爱好吗？
So is that, like, your thing?
‪随身带着吉他 提醒女孩子‪她们生活中的丢脸时刻？
Carry around a guitar and remind girls of horrible moments in their life?
‪我不是那个意思
I... I didn't mean it like that.
‪老实说 大家都在高声欢呼叫喊
To be honest, everyone was yelling and cheering so loud, I could barely hear
‪ -我几乎听不到你在说什么‪ -这是好消息
- what you were saying. - That is great news.
‪不要感到尴尬
Don't be embarrassed.
‪尴尬？
Embarrassed?
‪我没有尴尬 他竟然这样说
I... I am not embarrassed. Get a load of this guy!
‪我没有尴尬 没有
I am not embarrassed. No, no, no. I...
‪你应该尴尬 对的
You should be embarrassed. That's right.
‪我该为你的尴尬而向你道歉
And I should be apologizing to you for your embarrassment.
‪我也没有尴尬
Well, I wasn't embarrassed either.
‪我松了一口气‪虽然你说什么也没听到
That's a relief, for me, even though you said you couldn't hear anything.
‪ -对的‪ -嗯
- Exactly. - So, yeah.
‪不管怎样 幸会
‪但我有点饿 所以…
Anyway, nice to meet you, but I'm a little hungry, so...
‪我要去搞点零食
I'm gonna go get myself a snack.
‪可恶
Damn it.
‪（返校日）
‪那边发生什么事了？
What's going on over there?
我不知道
I don't know.
‪似乎你被提名为返校日国王了
It looks like you got nominated for Homecoming King.
‪ -什么？‪ -谁把你的名字写在选票上？
What?
谁把你的名字写在选票上的？
Who the hell put your name on the ballot?
‪是我
I did.
‪干得好 小弗林
‪太可爱了
- Nice work, Tiny Flynn. - Oh, you look so cute!
‪ -嘿 美女‪ -嘿 很高兴你来了
- Hey, pretty lady! - Hey. Oh, I'm glad you're here.
‪今天有个波士顿的包裹‪上面写着你的名字
A package arrived today with your name on it from Boston.
‪什么？天啊
What? Oh, my gosh!
‪天啊 这太可爱了
Oh, my gosh! This is so cute!
‪我爱它
Oh, I love it!
‪噢 还有张卡片
Ooh, there's a card!
‪艾莉 给你寄了件兜帽衫‪你来波士顿的时候可以保暖
Elle, sent you a hoodie to keep you warm for your trip to Boston.
‪如果你要来的话
If you're up for it.
‪等等 什么？
Wait, what?
‪噢 我的天 是去波士顿的机票
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my God, it's a ticket to Boston!
‪你会喜欢那里的
- You're gonna love it there! - Oh!
‪你会来吗？
So, can you make it?
‪嗒哒
Ta-da!
‪我的答案是百分百的好
So, my answer is a firm yes!
‪对 好的 我觉得这是负责任的选择
Yeah, okay. I think that's the responsible choice.
‪我想你是对的 不然我怎么能…
Well, I guess you're right, because how else would I be able
‪ -参加所有大学的面试？‪ -等等 你在申请这里的学校？
- to do all my college interviews? - Wait, you're applying to schools here?
‪我已经向波士顿的大学发了申请
I already sent out applications to Boston University,
‪塔夫茨大学 波士顿学院…
Tufts, Boston College...
‪还有哈佛？
And Harvard?
‪是的 还有哈佛大学
Yes, and Harvard.
‪ -诺亚 来吧 我们要走了‪ -太棒了
- Noah, come on! - Brilliant!
我们出发
We're going.
‪该死 很抱歉‪我忘了今天要去卡拉OK
‪我要去准备
Shit, I'm so sorry. I forgot, I've got some karaoke today. Gotta get ready.
‪各位 跟艾莉打招呼
Guys, yo, say hello to Elle.
‪嗨 艾莉
- Oh. - Hi, Elle!
‪嗨
Hi!
‪ -你们好‪ -克洛伊 你好吗？
- Hello, boys! - Chloe, how are you?
‪今晚谁来唱歌？
So, who's singing tonight, then?
‪是吗？天啊 穿上衣服 裸男
Yes? Oh, my God. Get dressed, naked boy.
‪太丢人了
Scandalous!
‪嘿 宝贝 很抱歉 这是好消息
Hey, babe, I'm sorry. This is, uh... This is great news,
‪但我要走了 明天再细谈好吗？
but I gotta go, so we can talk about this tomorrow?
‪好 当然
Okay, sure...
‪ -好的 再见‪ -我很期待见到…
- All right, bye. - I can't wait to meet...
‪大家
everyone.
‪好了 来吧
Okay, here we go.
‪我知道我会后悔的
I know I'm gonna regret this.
‪克洛伊·温思罗普
"Chloe Winthrop."
‪对 就是那种最典型‪让人惊艳的超模女神
Oh, just your run-of-the-mill, breathtaking supermodel goddess.
‪完全不用担心
No worries there.
‪（哈佛的学费和生活费）
‪我不确定想看这个…
Not sure I even wanna see this...
‪该死 那是一大笔钱
Holy crap! That's a lot of money.
‪唉
Oh, boy.
‪就是彼此相守
"Is each other."
‪就是那天晚上
‪我决定要抓紧诺亚
It was that night I decided to hold on to Noah.
‪ -嘿 爸爸？‪ -什么？
- Hey, Dad. - Yeah.
‪我能和你谈一下吗？
Could I talk to you for a second?
‪是的 当然 说吧
Yeah, sure. Shoot.
‪是关于学校的事
Um, it's just about school.
‪我想知道有多少… 搞清楚‪我们要…
I just want to know how much we, like... Figure out, what do we, like, have to...
‪我们有多少钱交学费
How much money we have for tuition.
‪是的
Yeah, um...
‪我想我需要知道
I kinda think I need to know.
‪你知道 我…
You know, I...
‪我以为你想去加州大学伯克利分校
I thought you wanted to go to UC Berkeley.
‪是的 我只是…
No, I do, I do. It's just...
‪我想申请一些后备学校会比较好
you know, I think it's smart to apply to some backup schools too.
‪有些学校是私立的
And some of those schools are private.
‪你知道 没有财务支持和你的帮助
You know, without some sort of financial aid and your help,
‪我不太确定我们能负担更贵的大学
I'm not so sure we can afford a more expensive college.
‪别忘了我还要支付布拉德的学费
Don't forget I still have to pay for Brad's school.
‪我没想到这点
Oh... I didn't think of that.
‪ -很抱歉 艾莉 如果我能…‪ -不 爸爸
- I'm sorry, Elle. You know, if I could... - Look, Dad,
‪我完全理解 没问题
I totally understand. It's not a problem.
‪好的
Okay.
‪这绝对是个问题
This is definitely a problem.
‪欢迎来到高中户外日
Welcome to Senior Field Day.
‪请来停车场报到并挑选你的队伍
Please report to the parking lot to pick your teams.
‪我们看看…
‪好吧 奥利
Let's see... Okay, Ollie...
‪好的 我在想接下来要选大块头
All right, I am thinking we go for poundage on this one, right?
‪比如 塔宾这样的
Like, Tuppen would just be so...
‪我理解你 但这次你能相信我吗？
I feel you, but can you trust me on this one?
‪迈尔斯排球打得非常好
Miles is phenomenal at volleyball.
‪学生会会长迈尔斯？
Student Council President Miles?
‪是的 他很棒
Yeah. He's amazing.
‪来吧 依云丝 快点 要选谁？
Let's go, Evans, come on. Who's it gonna be?
‪相信我
‪快点
- Trust me. - Let's go! Come on.
‪我们要选迈尔斯
Uh, we're gonna go with Miles!
‪ -好的 迈尔斯 你被选了‪ -我？
- Okay, Miles, you're up. - Me?
‪ -是的 你‪ -是的 你
Yeah, you.
‪这是队服 兄弟
Whoo! Here's a team shirt, my dude.
‪ -我们来吧‪ -马可 选谁？
- Let's do it. - And, Marco, who's it gonna be?
‪我们要那个大家伙
We'll take the big guy.
‪塔宾 他们选了塔宾
Tuppen. They've got Tuppen.
‪祝你好运 依云丝队长
Good luck, Capt. Evans.
‪我们没问题 我们很好
We're fine. We're good.
‪各就各位 准备
On your marks. Get set.
‪艾莉 你的鞋带松了
Elle, your shoe's untied.
‪什么？噢 谢谢
What? Oh, thanks.
‪冲
Go!
‪我真的被骗了吗？
Did I actually just fall for that?
‪冲啊
Go!
‪一、二、三 抛
One, two, three, toss!
‪冲啊
Go! Go! Go!
‪什么？
What!
‪天啊 拉
Oh, my God! Pull!
-兄弟 脱衣服‪ -现在？
Pull!
‪天啊
Oh, my gosh!
‪什么？
Whoa!
‪等等 不要 集中精神
- Oh! - No, focus!
‪好吧 他很厉害 我们来吧
All right, he's good. Whoo! Let's go!
好好好
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
‪ -上去‪ -冲啊
Come on, Elle!
‪要帮忙吗？
Need a hand?
‪不用
Oh! Hell no!
‪那你慢慢来 终点见
Have it your way. See you at the finish line!
你可以 快
You can do it! Come on!
‪嘿 既然我们来了
Hey, while we're down here,
‪我们能顺便去那个地方看看？
should we maybe go by that place with the thingy?
‪我的天 当然好 第21条规矩
Oh, my God! Of course. Rule number 21.
‪不好意思 兄弟 是第2条规矩
Should we do rule number 2?
‪ -但还有第4条规矩‪ -还有 嘿 第18条规矩
- But also rule number 4. - But also, hey! Rule number 18!
‪没错 天啊 说得对
- Exactly! Oh, my God! Exactly! - Whoo!
‪嘿 我想我要回家了
Hey, you know what? I think I'll head home.
‪真的吗？没事吧？
Really? Is everything okay?
‪没事 我只是不太舒服
Yeah, I'm just not feeling well.
‪噢 好吧
Oh, okay, yeah.
‪再见
Bye.
‪好好休息
Feel better.
‪谢谢
Thanks.
‪嘿 你们没事吧？
Hey, are you guys okay?
‪是的 我想是的
Uh, yeah, I... I think so.
‪我迟点给她打电话
I'd better just give her a call later.
‪好
Yeah.
‪你知道 艾莉
You know, Elle,
‪ -不好意思 我是最蠢的‪ -你从来没有…
- assuming I'm the dumbest person ever. - You used to never be good at this.
‪等等
Wait a second.
‪那是马可吗？
Is that Marco?
‪来吧
- Come on. -  It's what I like about you
‪好了 我们走吧
All right, let's go.
‪嘿 你们等等
Hey, guys! Hold up!
‪刚才很精彩 兄弟
That was really good, dude.
‪ -我印象深刻‪ -谢谢
- I'm impressed. - Thanks.
‪你觉得呢 艾莉？
What'd you think, Elle?
‪我的想法不重要 在我们看来
Oh, you know, my opinion doesn't really matter. I'm sure you're impressed
‪你完全可以自我陶醉
- with yourself enough for the both of us. - Oh!
‪你的朋友很不喜欢我
Your friend doesn't like me very much.
‪她还在为户外日输掉比赛不开心
She's still upset about losing on Field Day.
‪反正
- Oh! - Anyways,
‪周五你都是这样过的吗？
so, is this how you spend your Fridays?
‪用吉他炫技在圣塔莫尼卡撩妹？
Just wooing the women of Santa Monica with your fancy guitar?
‪有什么需要吗？
Any requests?
‪ -亲吻亭‪ -这样吧
- Kissing booth... - Know what?
‪很遗憾我们已经有安排了
That's a shame that we have made plans.
‪我们不想将你从那些‪仰慕你的粉丝身边带走
But we wouldn't wanna pull you away from your adoring fans,
‪我们迟点见 马可
so we'll see you later, Marco.
‪别这样对我
Don't do that to me! Come on!
‪我不会叫马可来摊位
I'm not asking Marco to do the booth.
‪ -我不愿意‪ -我跟你说
- I don't want to. - I'm telling you.
‪算了吧 我不会这么做
You know, give it a rest, man. I'm not doing it.
‪不是吧
No.
‪（第一名 MVP）
‪噢 该死的
Oh, son of a bitch!
I'm losing my mind In all this commotion
‪（错过）
Round and around That's the way it goes
‪（好 很好 错过）
I got the feeling That you got the feeling
‪（完美 很好 好）
Round and around That's the way it goes
‪（错过）
I've been believing That you've got the feeling
‪（很好 错过 完美 很好）
Round and around That's the way it goes
‪（好 完美 很好）
I've got the feeling That you've got the feeling
‪来吧 宝贝
Come on. Come on, baby.
‪（准确率96%）
‪噢 可能有机会
Ooh! That might do it!
‪（新的最高分 E+L）
‪好啊 我们还是做到了
- Yes! We still got it! - Whew!
‪我喜欢胜利的滋味
I love the smell of victory!
‪ -噢 我的天‪ -等等 我身上有味道吗？
- Oh, my goodness! - Wait! Do I smell?
‪ -不 你没有‪ -很好
- No, you're good. - Cool.
‪（舞蹈狂热终极对决）
‪（第一名 5万奖金）
‪就是这个
And there it was.
‪一种赚大钱的方法
A way to make a boatload of money
‪可以解决在波士顿读书的学费
that could help cover the cost of school in Boston.
‪这钱是实在的
‪无论我最终去了哪所学校
The money was real and could make things easier for Dad,
‪都可以减轻爸爸的负担
no matter which school I ended up getting into.
‪等等 你不会真的认为…
Wait, you're not actually thinking we could...
‪我们能赢得自由式比赛吧？
Uh, win the freestyle category?
‪这正是我在想的
That's exactly what I'm thinking.
‪事实上 我们玩得很不错 不是吗？
Well, actually, we are pretty good at this, aren't we?
‪很不错？我们的积分榜头名‪维持了四年
Pretty good? We've had the top score for four years.
‪我们还可以做队服
Ooh-ooh-ooh! We could even make team T-shirts.
‪对 队服 为何不呢？‪当然好 我很愿意
Yes! Team T-shirts! Why not? Sure! I love it!
‪但如果我们要做 就要好好做
But if we're gonna do it, we have to do this right, okay?
‪明天早上七点开始训练
Training starts tomorrow at seven a.m. sharp.
‪等等 训练？
Wait. Training?
‪（申请人个人论文）
‪“五年后你想成为什么人？”‪是个很难回答的问题
"What do you want to be in five years?"
‪因为当我想要搞清楚某件事
because as soon as I start to figure out one thing,
‪总有一些人或事发生变化‪让我质疑一切
something or someone changes and makes me question everything.
‪如果不能确定现在的自己
And if I'm not sure what I am right now,
‪我怎能确定五年后想变成怎样？
how could I possibly know what I want to be in five years?
‪嘿 是你
Hey, you!
‪嘿 很抱歉 有些家伙在我这边学习
Hey, I'm sorry. Some of the guys were over studying.
‪所以我没更早打给你
That's why I didn't call sooner.
‪别担心 我很高兴你在那边有朋友
No worries. I'm glad you're making friends out there.
‪再过两个晚上
And in two more sleeps,
‪我就能来见你 还能见到他们
I get to come see you and meet all of them.
‪对 但我们没必要整个周末‪和他们一起
Yeah, but we don't have to spend the entire weekend with them though.
‪不 我想了解他们
No, I want to get to know them.
‪嗯 至少是其中一个
Well, one of them, at least.
‪好了 开始吧
‪五、六、七、 八
Five, six, seven, eight.
‪一、二、三、四
One and two and three and four
‪五、六、七、 八
and five, six, seven, eight.
‪一、二、三、四
And one and two and three and four
‪ -五、六 哇‪ -抱歉
- and five, six... whoa! - Ugh, sorry!
‪天 我们该休息一下
God! We should take a break!
‪不要啦 我想在明天去波士顿之前
Come on, I just want to get in one more hour of practice
‪再多练习一小时
before I leave for Boston tomorrow.
‪我们只有九周时间做准备
We only have nine weeks to get ready!
‪你是不是有点太认真了？
Do you think that you're maybe just taking this, like, a little bit too seriously?
‪是很认真的
It is serious!
‪我没有…
I didn't...
‪我之前没想说 但是…
I didn't want to say anything before, but...
‪我真的需要这笔钱读大学
I really need the money for school.
‪我们来吧
Let's do it.
‪噢 天 看谁在这里
Oh, God! Look who's here.
‪噢 太完美了 我们需要展位的主角
Ooh! This is perfect. We need a headliner for the booth.
‪ -不行‪ -所有人都迷恋他
- No! - Everyone's obsessed with him!
‪为什么？
Why?
‪你承诺了要有最性感的吻者
You promised the hottest kissers.
‪就像去年你得到他 所有人都来排队
Like last year, you get him, everyone else will just fall in line.
‪别挡路
‪嘿
Hey!
‪到处都看到你们在一起
You two do go everywhere together.
‪是的
Uh, yeah, yeah, we do.
‪反正 我… 抱歉
Anyway, uh, I... sorry.
‪我们想找你帮忙
We wanted to, uh, ask you something.
‪我们在返校日的筹款活动‪有一个亲吻亭
We do this kissing booth at the Homecoming fundraiser,
‪我们想问你是否愿意做‪今年其中一名吻者
and we were wondering if you'd be one of our kissers this year.
‪不愿意
No.
‪不愿意？为什么？
‪ -我有我的理由‪ -别这样 兄弟
- I have my reasons. - Come on, dude!
‪这是最受欢迎的展位
It's the most popular booth!
‪这是为了慈善事业
And it's for charity.
‪你不相信慈善吗？
Don't you believe in charity?
‪我正在跟你说话
- I'm standing here talking to you. - Hey! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
‪那真是个好例子
That was a good... one.
‪好的
Okay.
‪我跟你做个交易
I'll make you a deal.
‪我可以在这里跟你玩任何游戏
I'll play you any game here for it.
‪天啊
Holy shit!
‪你赢了 我就参加
You win, I do the booth.
‪我赢了
I win,
‪你要免费照看我妹妹
you babysit my sister for free.
‪我跟我同事商量下
Let me talk with my colleague.
‪好吧
Okay. Fine.
‪任何游戏
Uh... any game.
‪现在来设置陷阱
And now to set the trap.
‪任何游戏 除了那个
Any game except... that one.
‪ -不行‪ -好吧 但是那个…
‪我说的是任何游戏
- No, no, no. I said any game. - Okay, but that one's...
‪嗯 对 但那个真是太难了
Well, yeah, but that one's so hard.
‪好了
Bingo!
‪好吧 没问题
Okay, all right. Fine.
‪天啊 我们把他弄到了目标地方
Oh, my God! We got him right where we want him!
‪ -好的‪ -好的
All righty.
‪开始吧
Here you go.
‪（很好 完美）
And if you want a shot Then it's coming through me...
‪ -嘿 兄弟 你姓什么？‪ -佩尼亚
- Uh, hey, dude, what's your last name? - Peña.
‪中间名 瓦伦汀
Middle name, Valentin.
‪MVP？
MVP?
‪天啊
Oh, my God!
‪（很好 完美）
Everybody wants to be the Everybody wants to be the best
‪ -好啊‪ -好啊
- Yeah! Yes! Yes! - Yes! Yes!
‪（玩家1 获胜）
‪ -天啊 太好了‪ -太好了
- Yes! - Oh, my gosh! Yes!
‪你周五晚就是这样过的吗？‪在跳舞机上骗人？
Is this how you spend your Friday nights? Conning people on the DDM machine?
‪我们在展位见 MVP 噢
See you at the booth, MVP! Oh, and, um...
‪你可以把吉他留在家里
you can leave the guitar at home.
‪好啊
See ya!
‪天啊 太疯狂了
Oh, my gosh, that was crazy!
‪ -我们搞定了马可‪ -搞定了
- We got Marco! - You got Marco.
‪ -‪我们还有要你命女孩‪ -当然
- And we have the OMGs. - Definitely.
‪ -你觉得瑞秋愿意参加吗？‪ -噢 该死 瑞秋
- And you think Rachel would do it? - Oh, shit! Rachel!
‪ -什么？‪ -不是吧
- What? - No, no, no!
‪我今晚约了瑞秋
No, no, I was supposed to hang out with Rachel tonight.
‪ -我马上要走了 再见‪ -好 去吧
- I have to leave right now! Bye! - Yeah, go, go!
‪我很抱歉 我和艾莉一起练习
I'm so sorry.
I was practicing with Elle.
‪听着 李尔
Look, Lee.
‪我知道艾莉是你最好的朋友
‪但以后不能这样了
I know that Elle is your best friend, but this has gotta stop.
‪ -我是说 自从诺亚离开‪ -她总是在身边
- I mean, ever since Noah left... - She's always around.
‪真的 你要跟她说说
Exactly! You gotta say something to her.
‪我知道 对不起‪但请不要怪她 好吗？
I know, and I'm sorry, but please don't blame her for this, okay?
‪是我忘记了
I'm the one who forgot.
‪不只是今晚
But it's not just tonight.
‪她总是不请自来 或者突然出现
She's always inviting herself or just showing up.
‪她很孤单 我不能跟她说‪我们不想她和我们出去
She's lonely! I can't tell her we don't want her hanging out with us.
‪但你让我在电影院
But you can leave me standing at the movie theater
‪傻站45分钟就没问题？
for 45 minutes just fine?
‪听着 李尔 如果你…
Listen, Lee. If you...
‪如果你不能让你最好的朋友
if you can't make your best friend understand
‪理解这段关系的重要性
that this relationship is important,
‪那我想 我们的关系可有可无
then I don't think we have a relationship.
‪ -瑞秋 我不能告诉她…‪ -搞清楚哪个重要 李尔
- Rachel, I can't just tell her... - Just figure out your priorities, Lee.
‪如果我很重要 你就去告诉艾莉
If I'm one of them, then go and tell Elle that I am.
‪晚安
Good night.
‪我真不敢相信 你迟到一次‪她就那么生气
I can't believe she got that mad about you being late one time.
‪嗯
Well...
‪事情比这要复杂一点
it's a little bit more complicated than that.
‪你没事吧？
You okay?
‪我只是对波士顿有点紧张
I'm just a little nervous about Boston.
‪别担心
Don't worry about it.
‪只有诺亚
It's just Noah.
‪对
Yeah.
‪ -我爱你‪ -我爱你
I love you.
‪ -你回来后再见了 好吗？‪ -好
- I love you. - See you when you're back, yeah?
‪ -再见‪ -再见
- Yep. Bye. - Bye.
‪当你有段时间没见到某人
But when it's been a while since you've seen someone,
‪你确实会担心
you do worry.
‪担心自己放松了警惕
You worry you've let your guard down.
‪担心他们不想你
You worry they don't miss you.
‪如果过了一段时间 你甚至会担心
And if it's been a while,
‪自己忘记了如何亲吻他们
you even worry you forgot how to kiss them.
‪你什么都担心
You worry about everything.
‪那是我的男人
There's my guy.
‪（艾莉·依云丝）
‪（我更想你）
‪但现在
But now,
‪我一点也不担心了
I'm not worried about a damn thing.
‪你准备好来波士顿了吗？
You ready for Boston?
‪诺亚·弗林 你难以想象
Noah Flynn, you have no idea.
‪我不知道
I don't know.
‪我一直在想我现在的生活‪有多么不同
I just keep thinking about how different my life is right now.
‪你明白我的意思吗？
You know what I mean?
‪一想到我的面试 我就想吐了
And if I even think about my interviews, I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
‪艾莉 别说了
Elle, stop.
‪你会打动他们的
‪好吗？
You're gonna blow 'em away. Okay?
‪谢谢 到时就知道了
Well, thank you, but we'll see about that.
‪我要坦白说
Um.. Can I be honest real quickly?
‪等会我们离开后
Mm-hmm.
‪我在想 如果你不介意
I was thinking, like, if it's okay with you,
‪我会把你当做我的私人游乐场
I'm going to treat you like my own personal jungle gym.
‪埋单
Check!
‪我喜欢这个城市
I love this city.
‪我爱这个女孩
I love this girl.
‪在我们进去之前
So, just before we get in there,
‪这些家伙都很好
these guys are cool,
‪但他们会有点激动
but they are a little intense.
‪诺亚 我没事
Noah, I'm fine.
‪ -真的吗？‪ -是的
‪ -好吧‪ -来吧
- Okay? - Yes! Come on!
‪那案子完全不是这样的
Okay, that's not what that case was at all.
‪联合公民是司法哲学的经典例子‪对吗？
Oh, Citizens United was a classic example of judicial activism, right?
‪ -没错 正确‪ -多年来 保守派一直对…
- True. Correct. - After conservatives bellyached for years
‪ -自由至上主义满腹牢骚‪ -一样
- about the liberal Supremes. - Same thing.
‪ -你是最虚伪的人‪ -我说了他们很激动
- You are a hypocrite at its finest. - Told you they were intense!
‪不 那不是…
No! That was not...
‪我唯一想见的人不在这里
The only person I wanted to meet isn't here.
‪一个词和缩写
One word and an acronym!
‪不知道是不是故意的
I wonder if it was on purpose.
‪各位 看谁来了
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys! Look who's here.
‪詹姆斯
Oh, James!
‪这里的人她几乎都认识
She knows virtually everybody in here!
‪她真是长袖善舞
She knows how to work a room.
‪听说今晚你为我们准备了‪特别的东西？
‪我很兴奋
So I hear you got something special for us tonight? I'm excited.
‪ -你好‪ -嘿 你好吗？
- Hello, hello, hello! - Hey! How are you?
‪ -你气色很好 帅得很‪ -很高兴见到你
- You look so good! So dashing! - Nice to see you!
‪你好 美女
Oh, hello, gorgeous. Mmm!
‪ -很高兴见到你‪ -你很漂亮
- So good to see you. - You look beautiful.
‪谢谢
Thank you!
‪ -和我们一起吧‪ -谢谢你接我电话
- Come, join us! - Thanks for answering my call.
‪ -你去哪里了？‪ -我实在没有借口
- So, where were you? - I actually have no excuse,
‪我今晚会在舞池里补偿你
but I'll make it up to you tonight on the dance floor.
‪ -天啊 等等 这是艾莉？‪ -是的
- Oh, my God. Wait, no, is this Elle? - Yeah.
‪久仰大名 真的 天啊 你很漂亮
I have heard so much about you. Seriously. My God, you're gorgeous.
‪你…
You...
‪你真漂亮
You're gorgeous.
‪我马上就喜欢她了
I love her already.
‪可惜这个人长得太丑了 对吗？
Too bad this one here's so ugly, though, isn't it?
‪ -噢‪ -很受伤
- Oh! - Burn!
‪但他确实很听话 所以我留他在身边
But he does do as he's told, so I keep him around.
‪你肯定会的
- Oh! Oh, Noah. - I bet you do.
‪你去哪里了？
So, where were you?
‪今天真是个灾难
‪雕刻家退学了
So, today, total disaster. The sculptor dropped out...
‪我10岁时在津巴布韦
So, I'm in Zimbabwe, ten years old.
‪对 我妈在做关于‪恩德贝勒部落的研究
My mom was doing a research paper on the Ndebele tribe,
‪我们沿着赞比西河而行
and we're gliding down the Zambezi River,
‪突然间我们发现 身处在河马妈妈…
and suddenly, we realize we're in the middle of a mother hippo
‪和小河马中间 突然 嘴巴张开…
and a baby hippo, and suddenly, this mouth opens up...
‪ -走开‪ -嘣的一声
- Get out of here! - Out of nowhere and bam!
‪咬掉了船头 然后船开始下沉
Bit off the front of the boat! So, the boat starts sinking,
‪大家都往岸边游去 我妈说
and everyone is swimming to the side, and my mother's like,
‪克洛伊 你没事吧？
"Chloe, Chloe, Chloe, are you okay?"
‪我睁开眼睛 说道…
I open my eyes and I'm like...
‪ -能再去一次吗？‪ -不可能
- "Can we go again?" - No way! You are insane.
‪你是台机器
‪好了 来干了
All right! Shots!
‪ -干了‪ -干了
Shots, shots!
‪不好意思 我们该走了
You know, we actually... we need to go.
‪不是吧 这么早？
No! So early?
‪不是 艾莉明天要去学校面试 所以…
No. Elle's got college interviews tomorrow, so...
‪好吧 既然如此
Well, in that case,
‪祝艾莉明天面试有出色表现
here's to Elle kicking ass at her interviews tomorrow.
‪ -来吧‪ -敬艾莉
- Let's do it. - To Elle.
‪ -敬艾莉‪ -谢谢
- To Elle! - You're welcome.
‪你不知道我想胜过谁
Hmm. Tell you whose ass I'd like to kick.
‪依云丝小姐 事情大概就是这样了
Well, Miss Evans, that seems to be about it.
‪感谢你今天来和我们见面
Thank you for coming in today to meet with us.
‪谢谢你的邀请 这是我的荣幸
Thank you for having me. It was a pleasure.
‪ -艾莉‪ -什么事？
- Elle. - Yeah.
‪你介意我给你个建议吗？
Do you mind if I give you a piece of advice?
‪我有种感觉 我的很多问题
I had the feeling that you were searching
‪你都找了完美的答案
for the perfect answer to a lot of my questions.
‪你要知道 你似乎在努力迎合‪我们的期望
You should know that we're less interested in meeting the person
‪但我们对此并不感兴趣
you think we want you to be
‪我们只是想了解真正的你
and far more interested in getting to know the person you really are.
‪谢谢
Thank you.
‪（克洛伊 迟点出来见面好吗？）
‪（ -你该让我补偿你‪ -我想到了）
‪（ -我要洗个热水澡‪ -对 我湿透了）
‪喂
Hello.
‪怎么了？
What's going on?
‪没事吧？
Is everything okay?
‪我要去机场了
Gotta get to the airport.
‪告诉我 怎么了？
Talk to me. What's up?
‪如果你想找人聊天 就看看你的手机
If you wanna talk to someone, just check your phone.
‪艾莉
Elle! Elle!
‪生活向你扔出了曲球
Life throws curves at you.
‪你以为是一个方向
You think it's moving one way,
‪然后突然发现向着相反方向
and suddenly realize it's heading back in the opposite direction.
‪所以 很难预测五年后你想要什么
So it's difficult to know what you'll want in five years.
‪当曲球向你飞来
When that curve comes flying at you
‪你不确定该击打
and you're not sure whether you should try to hit it,
‪接住它 还是避开
catch it, or just step out of the way.
‪爸爸 我只是想了解我的选择 好吗？
Dad, I just wanted to explore my options, okay?
‪艾莉
‪跟这些没关系
Elle, it's not about any of that.
‪重要的是问你自己
It's about you asking yourself
‪你觉得和诺亚的关系会否持续
if you think a relationship with Noah's gonna last
‪为他改变你所有的计划是否值得
and if it's worth changing all of your plans for him.
‪你觉得呢？
Do you?
‪我不确定
I'm not sure.
‪嘿
Hey.
‪我觉得我们该谈谈
I figured that we should talk.
‪你走的时候为何这么难过？
Why were you so upset when you left?
‪嗯
Well, um...
‪我想我看到了你没有我的生活
I guess I was looking at this whole life that you have out there without me
‪而我…
and I'm...
‪我肯定不习惯看到‪你围着那些大学女生转
I'm definitely not used to seeing you around all those college girls.
‪艾莉 我跟你说 克洛伊只是一个朋友
Elle, I told you, Chloe's just a friend.
‪你怎么知道我说的是她？
How did you know I meant her?
‪好吧
Okay.
‪你听起来不太肯定
You don't sound convinced.
‪我想相信你
I wanna believe you.
‪你没理由不信我的
Well, there's no reason you shouldn't.
‪除了一个原因
Except one reason.
‪如果你告诉我没事发生
If you're telling me thatnothing has happened...
‪我会信你的
then I believe you.
‪好的
Good.
‪你知道我爱你
You know I love you.
‪我也爱你
I love you too.
‪很高兴我们把话说开
I'm really glad we talked.
‪ -我明天再打给你 好吗？‪ -好的
- I'll call you tomorrow, okay? - Okay.
‪嘿
Hey.
‪噢 你好 帅哥
‪我在外面 让我进来？
Oh, hello, handsome. I'm outside. Buzz me up?
‪好的 你等一下
Yeah, okay. See you in a bit.
‪ -做什么？‪ -你 亲爱的
‪自从艾莉走后 你超级无聊的‪所以我要带你出去玩
- Uh... what is this? - You, my dear,
have been a magnificent bore since Elle left, so I'm taking you out for some fun.
‪我觉得你对我很好
I think you're good for me.
‪说点我不知道的事
Tell me something I don't know.
‪该死 很抱歉 艾莉
Damn it! I'm so sorry, Elle!
‪没事 好的
That's okay. All right.
‪ -我就是做不到这个‪ -你可以的
- I just can't get this! - Yes, you can. Yes, you can.
‪ -我知道你可以‪ -我知道这对你有多重要
- I know you will. - I know how much this means to you.
‪我讨厌自己让你失望
I hate that I'm letting you down.
‪嘿 李尔 看着我
Hey, Lee, hey! Look at me.
‪你的人生一直害我跌倒
You have literally been letting me down your entire life.
‪天啊
Oh, man.
‪跟诺亚怎样了？
So, how was it with Noah?
‪我想他可能…
I think he might be...
‪我想告诉李尔关于诺亚的一切
I wanted to tell Lee everything about Noah,
‪耳环 甚至我的面试
the earring, even my interviews,
‪但老实说 我不知道从何说起
but honestly, I didn't even know where to begin.
‪很好玩 对 我们一起很开心
It was so fun. Yeah, we had a really good time.
‪ -好吧‪ -瑞秋呢？怎么样？
- Okay. - How about Rachel? How's that?
‪跟你走之前差不多
Uh, pretty much the same as before you left.
‪很抱歉
‪不过别担心
I'm sorry. Don't worry, though.
‪你会想到办法让她回心转意的
You'll come up with something to make her come around.
‪是的
Yeah.
‪对 我会的
Yeah, I will.
‪要练习吗？
Wanna practice?
‪ -来吧‪ -好的 很好
- Let's do it! - Okay, cool.
‪然后我失手‪什么时候不该让你跌倒？
And then drop you. When do I not drop you?
‪ -噢 对的 不能失手‪ -你不能让我跌倒
- Oh, that's right. Ever. - That part where you don't drop me.
‪五、六、七、八
Five, six, seven, eight.
‪一、二、三、四、五、六
‪七、八…
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
You belong out here with me You belong out here...
‪噢 我的天 你没事吧？
Oh, my God, are you okay?
‪哇 你没事吧？
- Ow! - Whoa! Are you okay?
‪ -我的脚踝‪ -好了 我帮你拿点冰
- My ankle! - Let me get you some ice.
‪该死
Damn it!
‪你觉得怎样？
How's that feel?
‪ -好点了‪ -好的
- Better. - Okay.
‪听着 艾莉 比赛的事很抱歉
Listen, Elle, I am so sorry about the competition.
‪没关系
It's okay.
‪等等 事实上…
Wait, actually...
‪你知道谁完全可以代替我？
you know who could totally replace me?
‪不行
No, no, no!
‪对 MVP 来吧 他很完美
Yeah, yes! MVP! Come on! He's perfect!
‪不行
No!
‪你不是还需要上大学的钱吗？
Don't you still need the money for school?
‪是的 但是…
Yeah, but...
‪他比我跳得更好 我们都知道
Well, he's better than me, and we both know it.
‪跟他组合 你就能赢
With him, you could actually win.
‪ -嗯 他不会这么做的‪ -我会让他答应
- Well, he's not gonna wanna do it. - I'll get him to do it.
‪我不会做的
There's no way I'm gonna do it.
‪为什么？
Why not?
‪我已经很不情愿加入亲吻亭‪现在又来这个？
I'm already doing your kissing booth, which I didn't want to do, and now this?
‪因为我的脚踝 我才请你帮忙
I'm only asking 'cause of my ankle.
‪ -我不相信她会想跟我搭档‪ -不是 她想的
- I can't believe she'd want me to do it. - No, she does.
‪她知道你有多出色
She knows how good you are.
‪ -她真的很想你帮忙‪ -真的吗？
- And she really wants you to. - Really?
‪ -嘿‪ -噢 嘿
Hey.
‪ -怎么了？‪ -他答应了
- So what is it? - He'll do it.
‪ -没有 他真的想参加‪ -真的？
- What did you have to do? - Nothing! He really wanted to.Really?
‪你来了
There you are.
‪我来了
I'm here.
‪好吧
Great.
‪首先 我想说
First of all, I just wanted to say
‪谢谢你代替李尔
thank you for filling in for Lee.
‪我想我们可以从舞步开始
So I thought we could start with the step patterns.
‪我是说 可以从这里开始
Yeah, I mean, I guess we could start there.
‪什么？
What?
‪我只是觉得先完成编舞
Well, I just thought it might be better to get the choreography down
‪再专注于舞步的准确度会更好
and then focus on the step accuracy.
‪听着 我看了几个小时的比赛
Listen, I've watched hours of these competitions,
‪获胜者的舞步总是近乎完美
and the winners always have near-perfect footwork.
‪但在自由式中 舞步准确度是给定的
But in freestyle, the step accuracy is a given.
‪是编舞能赢得评委的青睐
It's the choreography that wins over the judges.
‪没错 所以我们要从舞步开始
Yeah, exactly, which is why we're going to start with the step patterns
‪然后再进行编舞 好吗？
and then go to choreography, okay?
‪好的
Okay.
‪很好
Great.
‪如果你想要这样的话
If that's the way you wanna do it.
‪早安 洛杉矶乡村日
Good morning, Los Angeles Country Day.
‪希望你们的服装都准备好了
Hope you all have your costumes ready
‪ -因为高年级学生…‪ -嘿
- because the seniors have secured... - Hey!
‪ -一个特别的地点…‪ -李尔在哪里？
- A very special venue... - Where's Lee?
‪下周末的万圣节晚会
For the Halloween gala next weekend!
‪我们的今日名言是威廉·莎士比亚…‪什么…？
Our quote of the day is brought to you by William Shakesp... what the...
‪ -还给我 不要 李尔‪ -很抱歉 维维安
- Give it back! Don't, Lee! - Sorry. I'm sorry. Vivian!
‪ -还给我‪ -抱歉 维维安 拜托
- Give that back! - I'm sorry. Vivian, please, please!
‪很抱歉 我需要点时间
I'm sorry. I just need a second.
‪谢谢
Thank you.
‪瑞秋 是我 李尔 李尔·弗林
Hey, Rachel, it's me, Lee. Lee Flynn.
‪听着 我肯定会为此被罚留堂
Look, I'm uh... I am totally getting detention for this,
‪但这是值得的‪因为我真的要和你谈谈
but it's worth it because I really just needed to talk to you.
‪我对之前的事感到很抱歉
I am so, so sorry about everything that happened,
‪但最重要的
‪我想让你知道
but most importantly, I wanted you to know something.
‪我从未说过 但是…
I never told you this before, but...
‪我爱你 瑞秋
I love you, Rachel.
‪我真的希望你也爱我
And I'm really hoping that you love me too.
‪请给我发个微笑表情代表“是”
So would you please text me a smiley face emoji for yes
‪发个大便表情代表“不” 好吗？
and a poop emoji for no, please?
‪好了 弗林先生 表演结束了
All right, Mr. Flynn. The show's over.
‪走吧 是时候留堂了
- Ahh. - Let's go. Time for detention.
‪ -走吧‪ -好吧
- Let's go. - Okay.
‪快点 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
‪好啊
‪我有个微笑表情
Yes! Whoo-hoo! I got a smiley face!
‪好啊
Yeah! Whoo!
‪我有微笑表情 没有大便
I got a smiley face! There's no poop! Ha ha ha!
‪这里没有大便
There's no poop here!
‪他说他会想到办法的
Hmm. He said he'd figure out a way.
‪看来李尔没有把所有事告诉我
Guess Lee doesn't tell me everything.
‪我很高兴你终于说了
Well, I'm just glad you finally said it.
‪但我们之前说过
So, what we talked about,
‪艾莉总是在身边
Elle always being around,
‪你跟她谈过吗？
did you speak to her?
‪别担心 我会处理好
Don't worry. I took care of everything.
‪她会给我们足够的空间
She will be giving us plenty of space.
‪天啊 我喜欢你昨天的发言 李尔
Oh, my God, loved your speech yesterday, Lee.
‪这很火辣
It was hot.
‪谢谢 爱让我冲昏头脑
Thank you. I was driven by love.
‪瑞秋真是甜美可人
And Rachel is so sweet.
‪ -还有你 我很震惊‪ -太震惊了
- And you, I'd be devastated. - So devastated!
‪关于什么？
About what?
‪你还没看到照片墙上‪弗林那个新超模的照片？
You mean you haven't seen the Insta photos of Flynn's new supermodel?
‪再见 李尔
Bye, Lee.
‪有时有些事会在脑海里挥之不去
Sometimes there are things that get so stuck in your head,
‪只有一种方法将它们弄出来
that there's only one way to get them out.
‪我在健身房 回头打给你？
Hey, I'm at the gym. Can I call you back?
‪我现在要跟你谈谈
Um, I kinda need to talk to you now,
‪真的
actually.
‪好吧 怎么了？
Okay. What's up?
‪好了 我说了
Okay. Here I go.
‪我离开波士顿时
part of the reason I was so upset...
‪不开心的部分原因
when I left Boston
‪是因为我在你的房间里‪找到了一些东西
was because I found something in your room.
‪好的 你找到了什么？
Okay, what'd you find?
‪一只耳环
An earring,
‪在你床底下
under your bed,
‪我想知道这是不是克洛伊的
and I wondered if it belongs to Chloe.
‪艾莉 我保证
Elle, I promise you,
‪我完全不知道房间里怎么会有耳环
I have absolutely no idea how an earring got in my room.
‪可能是吧 但是… 它就在那里
That may be so, but... it was there...
‪好吧 我知道你的想法
Okay, I know what you thought.
‪但我没有跟克洛伊上床 好吗？
All right. But I'm not sleeping with Chloe, okay?
‪我保证 可能在我搬进去之前‪耳环就在了
I promise you. It could have been there before I moved in.
‪或者是我室友前任女友的‪有无数的可能
It could be my roommate's ex-girlfriend's. There's countless reasons.
‪考虑到你过去的表现 很难不去想
It's just that knowing your past, it's hard not to think...
‪这一点也不公平
That's not fair. At all.
‪你有什么理由怀疑我吗？
Have I ever given you reason to doubt me?
‪没有
No.
‪好的 那我请求你相信我
Okay. Then I'm asking you to trust me.
‪拜托
Please.
‪听到诺亚这样说 真是让人心碎
It was heartbreaking to hear Noah talk this way,
‪我知道我们关系怎样发展‪就取决于我的回答
and I knew everything for us depended on what I said next.
‪好吧
All right.
‪我相信你
I believe you.
‪好的
Okay.
‪我希望你早点说出来 但是…
I wish you'd brought it up sooner, but...
‪很高兴你告诉我
I'm glad you told me.
‪当你不确定自己的处境
When you're not sure where you stand,
‪有时候你只能赌一把
sometimes a leap of faith is the only move you can make.
‪等等 你错过了所有舞步
Okay, okay. Hang on, hang on, hang on. You're missing all the steps.
‪我们要怎么解决？
How can we fix that?
‪好吧 听着 我不担心这个
Okay, listen. I'm not worried about that. The precision will come.
‪准确度会有的 我们需要的是
‪真正能打动评委的东西
What we need is something that'll really blow the judges away.
‪我们连这个动作都做不好
We can't even get this routine right,
‪ -你想要搞得更复杂吗？‪ -我想要更有趣
- and you want to make it more complicated? - I want to make it more fun!
‪这是观众想要的
That's what the audience wants.
‪像这样的
Something like this.
‪天啊
Holy shit!
‪狡猾的家伙
Sneaky, sneaky boy.
‪穿帮了 你走得很好 不是吗？
Busted.
‪很抱歉 好吗？‪你和马可一起机会更大
I'm sorry. Okay? You had a better shot with Marco,
‪我知道你不会抛弃我‪所以我帮你一把
and I knew you wouldn't kick me off the team, so I did it for you.
‪你生气吗？
Are you mad?
‪不会 怎么会呢？
No. How could I be?
‪ -我们走吧‪ -好的
- Oh, let's go. - Okay.
‪闭嘴 我给你看受伤的脚踝是怎样的
Oh, shut up! I'll show you a hurt ankle.
‪你和马可最近怎样？
So, how is it going with Marco?
‪ -还不错‪ -真的？
- It is just fine. - Really?
‪不是 别问了
No. Don't even ask.
‪我知道我们要以棉花糖夹心饼的造型‪参加万圣节舞会
Oh! By the way, so I know we were gonna go as s'mores for the Halloween dance...
‪我们就选这个吧
I think we have a winner!
‪我对我们的万圣节服装有其他想法
But I have a different idea for our Halloween costume
‪我想给你看看
that I wanted to run by you.
‪看看我的背包
Check my bag.
‪比夹心饼更好？
Better than s'mores?
‪是的
Uh, yeah!
‪ -对吧？‪ -天啊
- Right? - Oh, my gosh!
‪ -我们要做吗？‪ -很明显
- Should we do it? - Obviously!
‪我就知道你会喜欢 我太了解你了
Knew you'd love it, I know you so frickin' well!
‪ -这肯定会赢‪ -我知道你会喜欢
- This is a winner. - I knew you'd love it.
‪我喜欢
Love it!
‪（诺亚 我们不是要谈谈吗？）
‪弗林的电话
Flynn's phone.
‪嗨 诺亚在吗？
Is, uh... is Noah around?
‪我想他去听音乐会了 他的手机没带
I think he went to a concert. I guess he left his phone here.
‪知道他跟谁去吗？
Any idea who he might have gone with?
‪应该是跟克洛伊
I think he went with Chloe.
‪好的 谢谢
okay, uh, thanks.
‪好吧 再见
All right. Bye.
‪真的吗？
Seriously?
‪有什么大不了？
What is the big deal?
‪天啊 问题是
‪还有四周就比赛了
Oh, my God! The big deal is that the competition is literally in four weeks
‪ -动作真是一场噩梦‪ -我觉得你太夸张了
- and the routine is a complete nightmare! - I think you're exaggerating.
‪不 听着 如果你不认真对待‪我们应该弃权
No, listen, if you don't want to take this seriously, we should just call it off.
‪好吧 暂停
Okay, time out.
‪我用了我所有的空闲时间
So I'm using every free hour I have,
‪为了帮你赢得比赛
practicing into the night for this competition
‪我排练到深夜
that you asked me to help you with,
‪难道是为了把事情搞砸？
just so I could screw things up for you?
‪不是
No.
‪不是 很抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
‪我现在有点麻烦事
I'm just kinda going through some stuff right now.
‪听着 你要相信我
Look, you have to trust me.
‪如果我们不开心‪评委的分数会反映出来
If we can't have fun, it's gonna show in our scores with the judges.
‪我很开心
I'm having fun.
‪真的吗？
Sure about that?
‪看看你自己 我录了下来
Watch yourself. I recorded us.
‪这里
Here.
‪天啊
Oh, my God.
‪别这样 你只是想太多了
You're just thinking too much.
‪你要放开点 感受音乐
You just gotta let go, feel the music.
‪你和李尔一开始为什么玩跳舞机？
Why did you and Lee start doing this in the first place?
‪因为很好玩
'Cause it was fun.
‪很抱歉我对你发泄不满
I'm sorry I've been giving you so much shit.
‪啊 没关系
Ah, it's okay.
‪我觉得真的要练习舞步了
I'm starting to think I really need to work on my footwork.
‪ -看这个‪ -闭嘴
- Shut up! - Look at this!
‪你饿吗？
You hungry?
‪ -我很高兴能休息一下‪ -就这一次
- I'm so glad we took a break. - Yeah, for once.
‪ -是呀 我可能太执着了‪ -你给自己很大压力
- I can be a little obsessive. - You put a lot of pressure on yourself.
‪是的 不然怎么能得到想要的？
Yeah, well how else are you gonna get what you want?
‪我不知道
I don't know.
‪我不喜欢做计划 我随遇而安
I don't like making plans. I just kinda roll with things.
‪是啊 但是…
Yeah, but...
‪你想做什么？
what do you wanna do?
‪不确定
Not sure.
‪我想是开心就行
Be happy, I guess.
‪但我要说 你启发了我
But I gotta say, you inspire me.
‪我？
Me?
‪你知道自己要什么 然后去追求它
You know what you want, and you go after it.
‪不 那是对我的错误印象
No.
‪我不知道我这辈子要做什么
I have no idea what I want to do with my life.
‪你能把事情做成
You make things happen.
‪我很佩服
I admire it.
‪我想说…
Well, I was gonna say that I...
‪我佩服你只是想要快乐
admire you for just wanting to be happy.
‪顺便说一下 我很感激你的帮助
I really am grateful for your help, by the way.
‪我并不富裕‪所以这有点像我的登月计划
I'm not exactly rich, so this is is kinda like my moonshot
‪能选择我想去的学校
to pick where I wanna go to school.
‪这是什么意思？
What do you mean?
‪这就像很棒的东西 你非常想要
It's like something amazing that you want really badly,
‪但不太可能发生
but it's not super likely to happen.
‪像是赢得跳舞机比赛
Like winning the DDM tournament.
‪不要有压力
No pressure.
‪登月计划
"Moonshot."
‪感觉很有压力
Feels like pressure.
‪说真的 是的 压力很大
Actually, it is. Yeah. Tons of pressure.
‪那么 诺亚在波士顿…
So... Noah's in Boston and...
‪我是说…
and I mean...
‪我不需要说细节 但有个女孩…
I don't need to get into all the details, but there's this girl...
‪你觉得他和她有关系？
And you think he's involved with her?
‪我不知道 我是说…
I don't know. I mean...
‪我是说 他说没有
I mean, he says he's not.
‪搞笑的是 当他离开时
It's funny 'cause when he left, I kinda had just assumed
‪我觉得他会遇到其他人
that he would meet someone else
‪然后我们就结束了 你知道吗？
and then it would just be over for us, you know?
‪你觉得你和诺亚是命中注定吗？
Do you think you and Noah were meant to be together?
‪我一直以为是的
I always thought we were.
‪但现在…
But now...
‪我不知道
I don't know.
‪就像我太用力去抓住…
It's like I'm trying so hard to hold on to this...
‪但还是感觉它慢慢溜走
thing, and it just feels like it's slipping away.
‪我不了解弗林
I don't know Flynn,
‪但如果我找到了我爱的人
but if I found someone who I loved,
‪一个聪明 有趣
that was smart and funny
‪和我有共同喜好的人
and liked the same stuff I liked,
‪我绝不会让她有这种感觉
I'd never make her feel like that.
‪不会让她跑掉的 对吗？
Wouldn't let her get away, huh?
‪我不会这样看
I don't see it like that.
‪你无法真正抓住一个人
You can't really hold on to someone.
‪因为你抓得越紧 他们就越想离开
'Cause the tighter you hold on to them, the more they wanna slip away.
‪你能做的就是去爱
All you can do is love them...
‪让他们知道 你永远不会离开
and make sure they know that you're never gonna slip away.
‪ -我不知道说得对不对‪ -不 你说得…
Uh, I don't know if I'm saying that right.
‪你说得很好
No, you're... saying it perfectly.
‪你要去万圣节舞会吗？
So are you gonna go to the Halloween dance?
‪我还没想好
I don't know yet.
‪噢 对了 抱歉 不做计划 我的错
‪对的
- Oh, right. Sorry, no plans. My bad. - Exactly.
‪期望会让你很难搞清楚‪自己想做什么样的人
Expectations make it difficult to figure out what you want to be,
‪因为不管是你认为会做的事
because whether it's something you thought you'd be doing...
‪还是你以为了解的人
Or someone you thought you knew.
‪嘿
Hey.
‪嘿 听着 很抱歉 我昨晚没打给你
Hey, listen, I'm sorry I didn't get to call you last night.
‪我出去了 手机忘在家里了
I went out, and I just left my phone at home.
‪没关系 玩得开心吗？
That's okay. Uh, did you have fun?
‪是的 很好 我们看到了很棒的乐队
Yeah, it was nice. We saw this pretty great band.
‪那很好
It was great.
‪很好
Cool.
‪你和谁一起去的？
Uh, who'd you go with?
‪噢 和几个兄弟
Uh, just some of the guys.
‪你的期望和真实发生的落差
The difference from what you expected
‪听起来很好玩
Sounds like a lot of fun.
‪是的
Yeah.
‪会让你以非常不同的方式看待未来
Can make you look at the future in a very different way.
‪来看看
Check it out!
‪你觉得如何？
What do you think?
‪什么？这太不公平了
- What? That's so unfair! - Oh!
‪ -我不知道我们…‪ -嗨 艾莉
- I didn't know we were, like, doing... - Hi, Elle.
‪噢 嘿 你好吗？
Oh, hey! How's it going?
‪看看我的傻南瓜 跟他的一比
Look at my stupid pumpkin, compared to his.
‪李尔 我以为我们今天要一起刻南瓜
Lee, I thought we were carving pumpkins today together.
‪我真的没法刻得更好
I can't even make this better.
‪噢 对 抱歉 艾莉和我有点玩过头了
Ah, yeah, sorry. Elle and I kinda got carried away.
‪好吧 我想我们可以走了
Okay, well, I guess we can just go, then.
‪好啊 我们要去哪里？
Cool, where we all going?
‪嘿 李尔 我们去散步吧
Hey, Lee, let's go for a walk.
‪好啊 我很愿意
Okay, yeah. I'd love to.
‪对 会很好玩的
Yeah! It'll be fun!
‪你怎样了？
How's it going?
‪噢 很好
Oh, yeah, good.
‪真的吗？
Really?
‪是的
Yeah.
‪为什么？你什么意思？
Why? What do you mean?
‪我希望你不介意我问 但是…
Well, I hope you don't mind me asking, but, um...
‪你和迈尔斯怎样了？
What's going on with you and Miles?
‪你什么意思？没事发生
What do you mean? There's nothing going on!
‪噢 好的 抱歉 我的错
Oh! Okay, sorry. My bad.
‪嘿 很抱歉
Hey, I'm sorry.
‪不 我错了 这不关我的事
No, no, I was wrong. It's none of my business.
‪是的 但是…
Yeah, but...
‪你没有错
you're not wrong.
‪你喜欢他？
So you're into him?
‪我不清楚 我不知道我怎么了‪我只是…
I don't know. I don't know what I am. I just...
‪我喜欢他
I like him.
‪我不知道为什么 看看他‪他就像…
I'm not even sure why. I mean, look at him. He's like...
‪他真是个呆子 对吧？
He's a total dork, right?
‪我不知道 他挺可爱的
I don't know. He's kind of adorable.
‪他真的很聪明
And he's really smart.
‪而且那些酒窝人畜无害
And those dimples definitely don't hurt.
‪是的
Yeah.
‪那你打算怎么办？
So what are you gonna do?
‪没什么 大概
Nothing, probably.
‪别跟任何人说
Please don't say anything to anybody.
‪我不会的 不会
I would never, no.
‪但是 奥利
But, Ollie,
‪你真不该在乎他们的想法
you really shouldn't care what the guys think.
‪你也不该让这些事阻止你
And you definitely shouldn't let it stop you
‪和你喜欢的人在一起
from being with someone that you like.
‪相信我 我很了解 这很糟糕
Believe me, I know all about that, and it sucks.
‪我喜欢带我的宝贝去看电影
I love to take my baby to a movie show
‪这样我可以在灯变暗的时候亲吻她
So I can try to smooch her...
‪但她并不喜欢浪漫爱情故事
But she won't cuddle To a story of romance...
‪拯救了城市 嘣 所以我们来这里
Whoo! Saved the city. Boom. That's why we're here.
‪噢 不
Oh, no!
‪噢 糟糕
Oh, shit!
‪ -李尔 你没告诉她？‪ -我完全忘了
- Lee, you didn't tell her? - I totally forgot!
‪瑞秋 对不起 我忘了跟你说‪我们换了服装
Rach, I'm so sorry, I forgot to tell you we changed our outfits!
‪ -没事‪ -糟糕
- It's fine. - Yikes!
‪当我抱着她 她就像一场梦
When I hold her, she's like a dream
‪如果她能听见有人尖叫
If only she can hear somebody scream
‪她不会在情人街停车
She doesn't go for parking down On Lovers' Lane
‪大量的月光 并没有让这个女孩变疯
And lots of moonlight Doesn't drive this girl insane
‪她认为梦幻音乐真的很无聊
She thinks that dreamy music Really is a bore
‪但我知道她在找什么
But I found out what she's looking for
‪需要蝙蝠侠、狼人、科学怪人‪或者德古拉
It takes the Batman, Wolfman Frankenstein or Dracula
‪才能让她温柔起来
To make her tender as can be
‪需要猫女和来自黑湖的狗男
It takes the Catgirl, Dogboy Creature from the Black Lagoon
‪才能让她和我上床
To get her making love with me
‪需要来自外太空的怪兽
It takes a Monster from Outer Space
‪才能让我的宝贝渴望我的拥抱
To make my baby want my embrace
‪当我抱着她
And when I hold her
‪她就像一场梦
She's like a dream
‪如果她能听见有人尖叫
If only she can hear somebody scream
‪啊 嘿 嘿
Yeah, hey, hey!
‪谢谢
Thank you!
‪嗯
Well, well, well.
‪这可比“也许我会来的”更隆重
This is a little bit more than "maybe I'll show up."
‪他们昨晚打电话给我‪问我能不能替补独奏吉他
Ah, they called me last night to see if I could cover for lead guitar.
‪既然我们都在这里
But since we're both here...
‪你想跳舞吗？
would you like to dance?
‪好啊 那挺好的
Yeah, that would be really nice.
‪ -她有男朋友‪ -他真大胆
She has a boyfriend.
‪放开自我 感受音乐
Just let go, feel the music.
‪我想她已经忘记弗林了
I guess she got over Flynn.
‪我们在做什么？一直在跳舞 对吗？
What are we doing? We dance all the time, right?
‪是的 别担心 我明白
- Oh. - Yeah, no worries, I understand.
‪我要回到台上了
I'm just gonna hop back in then.
‪好的
Okay.
‪再见
Bye!
‪嘿
Hey.
‪嗨
Hi.
‪不错的服装
Nice costume.
‪你也是
You too.
‪谢谢
Thanks.
‪我在想
So, I was thinking,
‪也许你和我可以…
maybe you and I could...
‪ -嘿 兄弟‪ -嘿 兄弟
- Whoo! Hey, dude. - Hey, dudes!
‪怎么回事？ 没什么 我们就是闲聊
- What's going on? - Uh, nothing, we're just chillin'.
‪ -反正 我们迟点见 迈尔斯‪ -好的
- Oh. - Anyway, I will see you later, Miles.
‪对 我们走吧 兄弟
- Okay. - Yeah. Let's go, boys.
‪好 再见
Yeah. See ya.
‪再见
Bye, guys.
‪噢 这是我的最爱 好啊
Oh! This is my jam! Okay!
‪天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
‪嘿 瑞秋怎样了？
Hey, what's up with Rachel?
‪ -她肯定还在生气‪ -让我去试试
- She must still be upset. - Let me. Let me try.
‪嘿
Hey.
‪ -怎么了？‪ -我没心情 艾莉
- What's going on? - I'm not in the mood, Elle.
‪瑞秋 我真的很抱歉搞错了服装
Rachel, I'm really, really sorry about the costume mix-up.
‪我让李尔在最后一刻将它换了
I had Lee switch it at the very last...
‪你就是不能听人说 对吗？
You just couldn't do as you were asked, could you?
‪什么？瑞秋
What? Rachel.
‪很抱歉 瑞秋 我不知道你在说什么
I'm sorry. Rachel, I don't really know what you're talking about.
‪ -我做了什么吗？‪ -什么？
- Did I do something? - Something?
‪你做了什么？
Did you do some thing?
‪你毁了我的舞会 你毁了保龄球之夜
You crashed my prom. You ruined bowling nights.
‪你将李尔的时间都浪费在‪你白痴的舞蹈游戏上
You wasted all of Lee's time with your stupid dance game.
‪天啊 艾莉 有你在周围
My God, Elle, with you around,
‪我简直没法和我的男朋友独处
I literally can't spend a moment alone with my own boyfriend!
‪瑞秋 我不知道你有这种感觉
Rachel, I had no idea that you were feeling this way...
‪你怎能站在这里睁眼说瞎话？
How can you stand there and say that when we both know it's a lie?
‪我要走了 我要回家 只有这样
I'm leaving now, and I'm going to my house because that's the only way
‪我才能和李尔一起
that I can spend time with Lee...
‪ -瑞秋‪ -没有你
- Rachel. - Without you!
‪瑞秋
Rachel...
‪我一开始就不想做该死的棉花糖
And I never wanted to be a friggin' marshmallow in the first place!
‪ -发生什么事？‪ -李尔 你要来吗？
- What happened? - Lee, are you coming?
‪走吧 我会找车回去
Go, go, go. I'll find a ride...
‪噢 天啊
Oh, boy.
‪（艾莉 能谈谈吗？我想消除误会）
Just to let me down, let me down And mess me around?
‪（开始）
‪嘿
‪（诺亚）
‪（等不及在感恩节见到你）
‪（嘿 你去了哪里？）
‪（抱歉 非常忙）
‪对不起 我不能说了‪你们是一对漂亮的夫妇
Sorry, I gotta stop here. You are a good-looking couple.
‪你像贾斯汀·比伯‪在他做卡车司机前的样子
You look like Justin Bieber before he started being a trucker.
‪（诺亚 要谈一下？）
‪要人陪吗？
Want some company?
‪当然
Sure.
‪（舞蹈狂热 步法图示）（很好 好 完美）
‪ -她追着我 “不要 看这个”‪ -天啊
‪（诺亚）
‪我很快回来 同学们
I'll be right back, class.
‪（我们今晚一定要谈谈 好吗？）
‪（好吧）
‪就像我说的 我知道我会后悔的
Like I said, I knew I'd come to regret this,
‪但一旦开始
but once you start,
‪真的很难停止
it's really hard to stop.
‪当你的心在往下沉的时候
That moment when your heart sinks,
‪我觉得就是这样
this is what it looked like for me.
‪在正式比赛前最后一次彩排
So, last rehearsal before the big day.
‪你感觉如何？
How you feeling?
‪很好
Yeah, good.
‪你确定？你看起来情绪低落
You sure? You seem a little off.
‪我没事 开始彩排吧 好吗？
I'm fine. Let's just rehearse, okay?
‪嘿
Hey. Hey.
‪看着我
Look at me.
‪放开自我 感受音乐
Just let go, feel the music.
‪好吗？
All right?
‪好的
Right.
‪放开自我
Just let go.
‪放手
Just let go...
‪我相信你
I believe you.
‪你似乎在努力迎合我们的期望
‪放手
We're less interested in meeting the person you think we want you to be
‪我们只是想了解真正的你
and far more interested in getting to know the person you really are.
‪放手
Let go!
‪好的 我想我们做到了
Okay, yeah, I think we got it.
‪我该走了
I should probably get going.
‪艾莉
Elle...
‪你的鞋带松了
your shoe's untied.
‪明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
‪登月计划
Moonshot.
‪ -喂？‪ -嘿
- Hello? - Hey.
‪你还好吧？
Is everything okay?
‪嗯 只是累了 我们一直在彩排
Yeah, um, just tired. We've been rehearsing.
‪好的 我只是想祝你明天比赛顺利
Okay, well, I just wanted to wish you luck for your competition tomorrow.
‪你还记得
You remembered.
‪对 我当然记得
Yeah, of course I remembered.
‪我希望能去
I wish I could be there.
‪艾莉 我知道我们之间
Elle, I know that, um... That you and I have some things
‪有些事情要讲清楚‪但我希望能面对面说
that we need to talk about, but I'd rather do it face-to-face.
‪我后天会回家过感恩节
So I'm gonna be home the day after tomorrow for Thanksgiving,
‪我想到时候 我们可以好好谈一次
and I guess we can talk about it all then.
‪好吗？
Okay?
‪诺亚说得对
Noah was right.
‪有些事只能当面说
Some things just need to be said in person.
‪好的
Okay.
‪欢迎来到西海岸 舞蹈狂热终极对决
Welcome to the West Coast Dance Dance Mania ultimate showdown.
‪这里有很多人 很多人观赛
There's a lot of people here, a lot of people to watch.
‪ -签到‪ -签到？
- Sign in. - Sign in?
‪看看这里的评委
‪（李尔）
Look at the judges here!
‪是李尔
It's Lee.
‪（技压全场 你的包忘在我车里了）
‪（正想知道它在哪里 谢谢）
‪ -准备好了吗？‪ -好了
- You ready? - Whoo! Okay.
‪ -他们很厉害‪ -是的
- They're really good. - Yeah.
‪哇
Wow.
‪我也喜欢他们的服装
Love their costumes too.
‪哇 他们准备充分
Wow, they came to win.
‪好的 依云丝 佩尼亚？
Okay, Evans, Peña.
‪你们是下一组
You're up next.
‪ -谢谢‪ -祝好运
- Thank you. - Good luck.
‪ -来吧‪ -好的
- Let's go. - Okay.
‪（如何申请哈佛大学）
‪怎么回事？
What the hell?
‪要享受快乐
Just have fun.
‪（准备 开始）
‪ -嘿 想要玩一下吗？‪ -你确定？
- Hey, you wanna have some fun? - You sure?
‪ -是的‪ -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
‪ -我们来吧‪ -准备好
- Let's do it. - Get ready.
‪天啊 看
Oh, my God! Look!
‪（100%舞步准确度）
‪你好 我是托妮 我是今晚的评委之一
Hello! I'm Toni. I'm one of your judges tonight
‪也是南加州大学
and a professor at the University of Southern California's.
‪互动媒体和电子游戏系的教授
Interactive Media and Video Gaming Department.
‪我非常兴奋能参与今年的活动
It's so exciting to be a part of the event this year.
‪这是迄今为止最激烈的比赛
This has been our fiercest competition yet.
‪我荣幸宣布 今年西海岸舞蹈狂热‪比赛冠军是…
I'm proud to announce that this year's winners of the DDM West Coast Jam are...
‪请热烈鼓掌
Drum roll, please.
‪艾莉·依云丝和马可·佩尼亚
Elle Evans and Marco Peña!
‪（舞蹈狂热终极对决冠军）
‪任何人想要搞清楚
Anyone trying to figure out
‪五年后自己是怎样的‪都会面对一个无可否认的事实
what they'll be in five years confronts one undeniable fact.
‪正如一位伟大的作家所说
Just as a great writer once said,
‪“地球之所以是圆的
"Perhaps the Earth was made round
‪是为了让我们无法看得太远”
so that we would not see too far down the road."
‪我们满怀希望和期待出发‪但当到达时
We set out on journeys full of hopes and expectations, but when we arrive,
‪终点永远不会像我们所想的那样
the destination never ends up looking exactly the way we had hoped it would.
‪艾莉 等等
‪请别跑
Elle, wait. Please, stop!
‪对不起 我现在没法应付这个
I'm sorry, but I just can't deal with this right now.
‪所以你打算对我们发生的事‪视而不见？
So you're just gonna ignore what's happening between us?
‪真的对不起 能迟点再说吗？拜托
I'm really sorry. Can we just please talk about this later? Please.
‪恭喜你
Congratulations.
‪第二天 诺亚还是没回我信息
The next day, Noah still wasn't answering my texts.
‪基于某种原因 李尔也没有
And for some reason, neither was Lee.
‪嘿 依云丝一家来了
- Hey! The Evans clan arrives! - Hi!
‪希望在弗林家的感恩节晚餐
Hopefully, Thanksgiving dinner at the Flynns
‪能解决这两个问题
would take care of both problems.
‪你好吗？
‪等等 瑞秋
Wait! Rachel!
‪瑞秋 我一直发信息给你
Rachel, I've been trying to text you!
‪艾莉 我没心情
Elle, I'm not in the mood.
‪ -我知道你不高兴 但是‪ -真的 艾莉
- I know that you're upset, but... - Seriously, Elle.
‪真的 你能和我谈谈吗？‪我不知道什么情况
Seriously, can you just talk to me? Like, I don't know what's going on.
‪大家感恩节快乐
‪感恩节快乐 李尔
- Happy Thanksgiving, y'all. - Happy Thanksgiving, Lee!
‪兄弟 怎么回事？瑞秋很生我气
Dude, what the hell? Rachel's still so pissed at me.
‪是的 我们两个都是
Yeah, well, that would make two of us.
‪你为什么生气？
Why are you mad?
‪噢 我不知道 可能这是答案
Oh, I don't know. Maybe the answer is in here.
‪该死
Shit!
‪天啊 等等 李尔 听我说
Gosh, wait, Lee. Listen to me. I'm...
‪ -我们回来了‪ -嘿
- We're back! - Hey!
‪ -啊 克洛伊 很高兴见到你‪ -噢 我也是
- Ah, Chloe! Good to finally meet you. - Well, it's lovely to meet you too.
‪进来吧
- Yeah. Come inside. - Ooh! Wow.
‪噢 艾莉 你来了
Oh, and Elle, you are here!
‪是的 你也是
Yeah, and so are you.
‪诺亚说他不确定你会不会来
Noah said he wasn't sure that you would be.
‪真的吗？他这样说吗？
Really? Is that what he said?
‪晚餐准备好了
Dinner's ready!
‪小心那些山药
Careful with those yams.
‪你会喝醉的
You're can get drunk off those.
‪李尔 你想聊两句吗？
Lee, do you wanna go talk for a second?
‪ -不太想‪ -我们能谈谈吗？
Not really, no.
‪谈谈 最好还是面对面
Talking. I always feel like talking's better when it's face-to-face.
‪ -李尔？‪ -克洛伊 听说波士顿很糟
- Lee. - So, Chloe, I hear Boston sucks.
‪我不知道该怎么回答
I'm not really sure how to answer that.
‪如果想住在那里 那没问题‪但你不该说谎
It's fine if that's where people want to live, but you shouldn't lie about it.
‪说谎 说谎是一个有趣的话题
Lying. Lying is an interesting topic of conversation.
‪当然 人们不会单独做决定
Of course, people aren't always making decisions alone.
‪有时他们要被说服去做愚蠢的事
You know, sometimes they need convincing to do the really stupid shit.
‪ -李尔‪ -闭上你的嘴
- Lee! - You need to shut your mouth.
‪别把李尔扯进来
You need to leave Lee out of this.
‪你怎么好像觉得我做错事一样？
Why are you acting like I'm the one that did something wrong?
‪诺亚 你…
Noah, you...
‪你不会想现在说的
you don't wanna go there right now.
‪李尔 听着
And, Lee, listen.
‪我很抱歉申请了波士顿的学校‪还有 瑞秋
I am actually really sorry about applying to schools in Boston, and, Rachel,
‪我都不知道你为何生我的气
I don't even know why you're mad at me right now.
‪你就装作李尔从未跟你说
So you're just gonna pretend that Lee never told you
‪我们需要空间‪但你一直在我们身边？
that we needed space from you constantly hanging around us?
‪什么？
What?
‪李尔 你从未…
Lee, you never...
‪ -李尔 你从未这样说过‪ -有的 李尔 告诉她
- Lee, you never said that. - Yes, he did! Lee, tell her.
‪我想说 但是…
I tried to, but...
‪小瑞
Rach. Rach.
‪ -天啊… 我…‪ -小瑞
- Oh, my... I am so... - Rach.
‪谢谢你的邀请 只是…
Thank you for the invitation. I just...
‪ -瑞秋‪ -瑞秋
- Rachel. - Rachel.
‪瑞秋
Rachel.
‪瑞秋 别这样
Rachel. Rachel, please!
‪她是我最好的朋友
She's my best friend.
‪你骗了我
You lied to me!
‪你令我对她口不择言
And you let me say all of those horrible things to her.
‪生日派对上 艾莉跑出去
‪我听到你说的话
I heard what you said at your birthday party when Elle ran out.
‪艾莉 发生什么事？
Elle, what's wrong?
‪我跟着你们两个
I followed you two.
‪我爱你
I love you.
‪但做我最好的朋友
But being my best friend
‪不代表你有权利告诉我该爱谁
doesn't give you the right to tell me who I can love.
‪就像瑞秋
It's like with Rachel.
‪如果我不喜欢她呢？你会怎么做？
What if I didn't like having her around? What would you do then?
‪ -我想我会跟她分手‪ -不是 听着
- I guess I'd break up with her. - No, you see,
‪不能因为我不喜欢
you shouldn't have to do that
‪你就该这样做
just because I didn't want you to be with her.
‪但你不用跟我分手了
But you don't have to break up with me
‪我不能接受一段关系‪和你还有艾莉在一起
because I can't be in a relationship with you and Elle anymore.
‪这太离谱了
It's just too much.
‪瑞秋
Rachel.
‪我想感谢我的家人
I am grateful for family,
‪我的新朋友
my new friend,
‪还有…
and...
‪我的摩托车
my motorcycle.
‪好吧
‪艾莉？
Um, okay. Elle...
‪哇 真是很难接
Wow, what a tough act to follow.
‪我想想
Let's see.
‪我感谢我的家人
I'm thankful for my family,
‪感谢我有机会 赢得了一些学费
for that I just, you know, won some money for school,
‪还有 是的 天啊
and... oh, yeah, oh, my God,
‪谢天谢地
I am super-duper thankful
‪我找到了克洛伊的耳环
that, um, that I found Chloe's earring.
‪天啊 你在哪里找到的？
Oh, my God. Where did you find it?
‪在诺亚的床底
Under Noah's bed.
‪我最感谢的是 在我为了某人
But what I'm most thankful for is that I found the earring...
‪做出改变人生计划的傻事前‪我找到了这个耳环
before I did anything crazy, like rearrange my whole life for someone.
‪在我看来 你已经改变了人生计划
You know, it kind of looked to me like you'd already rearranged your life.
‪也许我们应该…
I think that maybe we should just...
‪晚餐很愉快 克洛伊 很高兴见到你
You know what? This has been lovely. Chloe, always a pleasure,
‪我想我也该走了 所以…
but I think it's time for me to head out too. So...
‪艾莉
Elle.
‪你去哪里？
Where are you going?
‪去修补一些真正值得的关系
To fix something that's actually worth saving.
‪诺亚走之后 我只是…孤独 你明白吗?
And with Noah gone, I was just... lonely, you know?
‪ -我都不知道自己…‪ -妨碍别人的好事？
- I didn't realize that I was even... - Cock-blocking?
‪不确实是否该这样形容 但我想是的
Not sure if I would have phrased it like that, but, yeah, I guess.
‪我觉得自己导致了你们分手
The idea that I had something to do with you guys breaking up,
‪ -我…‪ -不是 李尔的错
- I feel so... - No. Lee did this.
‪他还会这样做‪因为你对他来说很重要
And he'd do it again because that's how much you mean to him.
‪瑞秋 他很爱你
Rachel, he loves you so much.
‪现在我知道问题所在
And now that I know the problem,
‪ -我完全能解决‪ -艾莉
- I can absolutely fix... - Elle!
‪是第16条规矩
It's rule number 16.
‪你知道？
You know?
‪第16条规矩 当你好友需要你
Rule number 16: When your bestie needs you there,
‪你必须陪伴在身边
you need to be there for your bestie.
‪你知道我不明白什么？
You know what I can't figure out though?
‪你的耳环怎么在我床底下？
How did your earring get under my bed in the first place?
‪好吧 说到这个…
Okay, about that...
‪别生气
Um, don't get pissy,
‪你出城去看足球赛时
but when you were out of town for a football game, I...
‪我和杰森吵了一架 在你床上睡着了
sort of crashed at your place after getting into a fight with Jason
‪耳环肯定是那时候掉的
and the earring must have just fallen off then.
‪你为什么不告诉我？
Why wouldn't you tell me that?
‪ -只是…‪ -我说过别生气
- That's just... - I said don't get pissy.
‪现在知道发生了什么 我们能解决的
Now that we know what's happened, we can fix this.
‪是的 我不确定是否想这样做
Yeah, I'm not sure if I wanna fix it.
‪你知道 我一直在想那个吻
You know, I can't stop thinking about that kiss.
‪我不敢相信 她真的认为我劈腿了‪你知道吗？
I can't believe that she thought that I'd actually cheat on her, you know?
‪所以当初我们出去玩的时候‪我才撒谎
That's the reason I was lying about us hanging out in the first place.
‪我想避免这种情况
I was trying to avoid this whole situation.
‪听我说
Listen to me.
‪从艾莉的角度来看
Just to give you things from Elle's point of view,
‪你过去有很多风流情史 对吗？
you used to have quite the reputation, right?
‪艾莉不知道我是世间少数几个
And Elle has no idea that I am one of the few women on the planet
‪能对诺亚·弗林的魅力免疫的女人
immune to the charms of Noah Flynn.
‪然后她发现我的耳环‪这对远在美国另一侧
And then she finds my earring, which couldn't have been very helpful
‪思念男朋友的女人来说
to a woman who's missing her guy
‪这可不是什么好事
all the way on the other side of the country.
‪你对的时候真讨厌
I don't like it when you're right.
‪我偶尔会睡错地方
Well, I do sleep where I'm not supposed to from time to time,
‪但总的来说
but overall,
‪我是很有天赋的人
I'm a very talented individual.
‪我想我知道李尔在哪里
I think I know where Lee is.
‪我走之前 要我帮忙收拾吗？
- Can I help you before I go? Just... - No, no, no.
‪不用 我会搞定这些麻烦的
I'll take care of this mess.
‪你也要解决你的
You go take care of yours.
‪但是艾莉 在你走之前 我想说
But, Elle, before you go, I just want to say this afternoon,
‪今天下午 你们三个说了很多
I noticed the three of you doing a lot of talking
‪但可能没有倾听
and maybe not as much listening.
‪我只想告诉你
I just want to tell you make sure
‪你真的要听对方想说的话
that you really listen to what the other person has to say.
‪听他们说完 好吗？
Just hear them out, okay?
‪好的
Okay.
‪好吧
‪噢 我差点忘记
Oh! I almost forgot.
‪我想拿走一样东西
There's a thing I wanna take with me.
‪第19条规矩 你该告诉我申请了哈佛
Rule number 19.
‪我知道
I know.
‪ -很抱歉‪ -我以为你想去伯克利
- I'm sorry. - I thought you wanted to go to Berkeley.
‪是的
I do.
‪只是…
It's just...
‪离开诺亚身边比我想的
‪要难多了
Like, being away from Noah was so much harder than I thought it was gonna be.
‪你该告诉我瑞秋的感受
And you should have told me about how Rachel was feeling.
‪我本来想的 但只是…
I was going to, but I just...
‪看到诺亚离开后 你多么孤单
saw how lonely you were when Noah left.
‪你知道我会理解的
You know that I would have understood.
‪我没告诉你的真正原因是
Well, I guess the real reason I didn't tell you was...
‪因为我不想
because I didn't want to.
‪我总是想你在身边
I just always want you around.
‪ -李尔‪ -但我不能拒绝瑞秋
- Lee. - But then I couldn't say no to Rachel,
‪所以我假装受伤‪让你忙于和马可排练
pretended to hurt myself so that you'd be busy practicing with Marco,
‪这样我就能有时间和瑞秋约会
and then I would have time to hang out with Rachel.
‪现在你明白我去年的感受
Now you know how I felt last year.
‪我也不想选 但是…
I didn't want to choose either,
‪我必须做决定
but I had to make a choice.
‪嘿 还有件事
Hey, one more thing.
‪第5条规矩
Rule number 5.
‪你没将它带来
You did not bring it with you.
‪我当然带了 来吧
Of course I did. Come on.
‪我是什么 新手吗？
What am I, a rookie?
‪第5条规矩
RULE NUMBER 5:
‪和好友一起掰感恩节许愿骨
Always do the Thanksgiving wishbone with your bestie.
‪好吧
Okay.
‪希望瑞秋能再给我一次机会
Here's wishing that Rachel will give me a second chance.
‪也就这样了
So much for that.
‪好吧 我们花48小时来自怨自怜
All right, I'm giving us 48 hours to feel sorry for ourselves.
‪然后就是返校日 我们还要做亲吻亭
Then we have Homecoming and a kissing booth to do.
‪（马可 我们要谈谈）
‪欢迎来到返校日
Welcome to Homecoming!
‪美洲狮半场前触地得分
Touchdown Cougars just before halftime!
‪我看到诺亚和克洛伊还在
I see that Noah and Chloe are still here.
‪噢 对 他们明天晚上走
Oh, yeah. They, um... They leave tomorrow night.
‪好了各位 这是你们一直期待的时刻
All right, everyone!
‪返校日国王是…
And Homecoming King is...
‪李尔·弗林
Lee Flynn!
‪什么？哇 等等 什么？
What? What? Wait! Whoa!
‪ -我赢了‪ -是你 好啊
- I won! - That's you!
‪ -我要下去‪ -是的 天啊
- I gotta go down there! - Yes! Oh, my God!
‪我爱你 我从没怀疑过你‪有一点吧
- I love you, man! - I never doubted you! Little bit!
‪你有点为他骄傲
You are the problem.
‪我感到无比自豪 老实说
You ought to be proud, let's be honest!
‪跟你弟弟说恭喜他
Tell your brother congratulations.
‪你说什么？
‪我说恭喜他
- What did you say? - I said congratulations.
‪有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
‪你没资格跟我说话
You have no business talking to me.
‪哇
Wow.
‪有人说恭喜 你就准备打他
Someone says congratulations, and you're ready to fight him.
‪你确实有问题
You do have a problem.
‪我现在唯一的问题就是你
No, the only problem I have right now is you.
‪你不是来道贺的 承认吧
And you didn't come over here to say congratulations, so just admit it.
‪好了 我们走吧 诺亚
Okay, let's go, Noah.
‪诺亚
Noah.
Noah!
‪我们走吧
Let's go.
‪晚安
Good night.
‪各位先生女士们 提醒一下明天晚上
Ladies and gentlemen, a reminder for tomorrow night.
‪记得参加洛杉矶乡村日筹款嘉年华
‪非常好玩 不容错过
The LA Country Day Fiesta Fundraiser. Don't miss out on the fun.
‪好了 各位 亲吻亭现在开始营业了
All right, everybody!
‪好的 我们再来一次
All right, let's do this thing! Again!
‪（数学俱乐部）
‪（篮球俱乐部）
Twist shake shout...
‪还不错
You aren't bad!
‪很难相信已经一年了
Hard to believe it's been a year.
‪这应该是我跟瑞秋的周年纪念
It would have been my anniversary with Rachel.
‪我一定要这样做吗？
Do I really have to do this?
‪过来
Come here.
‪你可以的
You got this.
‪上啊 李尔
‪我想你
I missed you.
‪我也想你
I missed you too.
‪很抱歉 曾经让你觉得
I am so sorry for ever making you feel
‪你不是我生命里最重要的人
like anything less than the most important person in my life.
‪如果你再给我一次机会
If you give me another chance,
‪我保证绝不会…
I promise I will never...
‪再让你有这种感觉
make you feel that way ever again.
‪我很爱你
I love you so much.
‪我不想失去你
And I don't wanna lose you.
‪你不会的
You're not going to.
‪第5条规矩
Rule number 5:
‪和好友一起掰感恩节许愿骨
Always do the Thanksgiving wishbone with your bestie.
‪李尔不知道我们许了同样的愿望
Lee just didn't know that we both made the same wish.
‪整个机场的人都能看出来‪你非常可怜
Everyone in this entire airport can see that you are absolutely miserable.
‪你显然想要艾莉
You obviously want Elle.
‪作为你的朋友 我要求你去做点什么
So, as your friend, I have to demand that you do something about it.
‪有什么意义？
What's the point?
‪看着我
Look at me.
‪你爱她吗？
Do you love her?
‪我不想在机场跟你谈这个
I'm not talking to you about this in an airport.
‪不 够了
No. Stop it.
‪你爱她吗？
Do you love her?
‪是的
Yeah.
‪那就告诉她
Then tell her,
‪因为不告诉她是很傻的
because not telling her is just stupid.
‪你很傲慢
And you are arrogant
‪很固执
and stubborn
‪很讨厌
and a pain in the ass,
‪但你并不傻
but one thing that you're not is stupid.
‪奥利
Ollie! Ollie! Ollie! Ollie! Ollie! Ollie! Ollie!
Ollie! Ollie!
快点
Come on!
‪呆在这里
Stay right there!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
-我知道我们会 -发光 发光 发光
-  I know we will -  Shine, shine, shine, shine
哦 是的
Oh, yeah!
‪你没事吧？
Are you okay?
当战争陷入僵局
When the war's too hard to fight
我将是你的指路明灯
I will be your guiding light
‪你有票吗？
Do you have a ticket?
因为你不必一个人去
'Cause you don't have to go alone
因为我知道我们会渡过难关...
'Cause I know we'll get Through the storm...
‪天啊
Oh, my God!
我将为你疯狂
I will carry you...
‪天啊
Oh, my God!
我将为你指路
I will be your guiding light
我为你疯狂
I will carry you
好
Okay.
艾莉
Elle!
‪接吻 来吧
Kissin'! Here we go!
‪好的
Okay.
‪你好
Hello.
‪抱歉 我没想到又这么紧张 天啊
Sorry, I didn't realize I was gonna be this nervous again! Oh, my goodness!
‪但是别担心 我吃了三四次薄荷糖
But don't worry. I've had, like, three or four breath mints, so we are...
‪所以我们随时都可以的
We are good to go in that department.
‪好的
All right.
‪我只是希望我的票‪值得你花一分钟的时间
I was kinda just hoping my ticket is worth a minute of your time.
‪嗨
Hi.
‪我应该打给你的 抱歉
I should've called you. I'm sorry.
‪那天晚上和诺亚的事 我很抱歉‪那太傻了
I'm sorry about the other night with Noah. It was... it was stupid.
‪但你不能否认 我们之间有些真感情
But you can't deny there's something real between us.
‪我不知道那是什么
I don't know what it is.
‪也许我们只是一时冲动
Maybe we just got caught up in the moment or something,
‪ -因为我… 有…‪ -请别这样
- 'cause I... there's... - Please... please don't... do that.
‪我们是有感觉的
We felt something.
‪我知道
I know it.
‪不要害怕你的感觉
Don't be afraid of how you feel.
‪我知道害怕 会阻碍你得到‪真正想要的东西
I know how being afraid can hold you back from getting what you really want.
‪你以为我为什么要加入学生会？
Why do you think I joined the council?
‪你说得对
You're right.
‪我是对你有感觉
I do have feelings for you.
‪当我们接吻…
When we kissed...
‪是有些东西
there was something there.
‪但你不是我的真命天子
But you're not the one.
‪我不想伤害你
I really didn't mean to hurt you.
‪但你不是我自欺欺人的对象
But you're not the one that I'm lying to myself about.
‪所以我要去找他
And that's why I have to go, and I have to find him
‪搞清楚发生了什么事
and find out what really happened.
‪我要听他说完
I have to hear him out...
‪要让他知道
and make sure that he knows.
‪我不会溜走
I'm not slipping away.
‪再见 马可
Goodbye, Marco.
‪抱歉 让一下 抱歉
Sorry! Excuse me! Sorry! Sorry!
初入爱河的人
Beginners in the house of love
像发呆的公牛
Like bulls in a china shop
让我出去吧 我走得太快了
Let me cast out I'm moving way too fast
点与线终于有了联系
And a dotted line Was connected at last
没有头绪 没有方向
‪（出发大厅）
Without a clue, without a map
‪（波士顿 登机）
我们只是从来没问过
We just never bothered to ask
打扰一下
Excuse me!
如果你想逃跑
And if you wanna run away
我马上就去追你
I'll be running right after you
这是我们的大事 我只是离得不够近
This thing is bigger than us And I just can't get close enough
让我们疯狂...
So let's get crazy...
‪诺亚
Noah!
‪天啊 我很抱歉
Oh, my God! I'm so sorry.
‪ -你看起来很像…‪ -艾莉？
- You look so much like my... - Elle?
‪你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
‪哪里…诺亚在哪里？
Where's... where's Noah?
‪他走了 他去找你了
He left. He went looking for you.
‪等等 什么？
Wait, what?
‪听着 耳环不代表什么
Look, that earring was nothing.
‪你要相信我‪诺亚和我之间什么都没有
You've got to believe me, there is nothing going on between Noah and me.
‪你知道他为什么带我回家过感恩节？
Do you know why he brought me home for Thanksgiving?
‪他只是希望我在场 能和你成为朋友
He just wanted me there so that we could become friends.
‪噢 天啊
Oh, God.
‪ -我觉得自己很蠢‪ -他也是
- I feel so stupid. - So does he.
‪但他为你疯狂
But he is crazy about you.
‪你必须知道
You must know that.
‪是他吗？
Is that him?
‪他怎么说？
What did he say?
‪（亲吻亭）
‪他在亲吻亭
He's at the kissing booth.
‪（我们在那里见面？）
‪嗯 你还在等什么？
Well, what are you waiting for?
‪谢谢你 克洛伊
Thank you, Chloe.
‪祝你好运
Good luck.
我马上就去追你
I'll be running right after you
这是我们的大事 我只是离得不够近
This thing is bigger than us And I just can't get close enough
我只是跟你不够亲近
And I just can't get close enough To you
‪嘿 我真的要跟你谈谈
Hey, I really need to talk to you.
‪ -你什么都不用说‪ -我要说 不是 艾莉 拜托
- You don't even have to say anything. - No, Elle, please.
‪我必须要说
I need to say this.
‪当我开始这个学年
When I started this school year,
‪我觉得非常孤单
I was pretty lonely,
‪我的学业表现不太好
and I wasn't really doing so well in my classes.
‪为什么你都不说？
Why didn't you say anything?
‪因为我觉得很丢脸
'Cause I was embarrassed.
‪然后我遇到了克洛伊
Then I met, uh, Chloe,
‪她带我到处转 介绍我认识她的朋友
and she showed me around, introduced me to her friends and...
‪还有…
And...
‪我知道以前我经常取笑‪你和李尔的规矩
I know we used to make fun of you and Lee and your rules,
‪但我看到你们的友情
but I see what you guys have.
‪我想我内心某部分‪希望和她也能一样
I guess a part of me just kinda wanted to have the same thing with her.
‪诺亚
Noah.
‪然后当你不相信 她和我只是朋友
So then when you didn't believe that her and I could just be friends,
‪这让我想起 你以前对我的看法
it reminded me of what you used to think about me...
‪我不喜欢这样
And I didn't like that.
‪这就是…
That was...
‪不是因为你 而是因为
that was less about you and more just...
‪我将自己和她比较
I just compared myself to her.
‪在你离开的时候 我觉得我们会结束
And when you left, I just kind of figured that we would end,
‪所以当我找到耳环
so when I found the earring,
‪我将这当做是结束的信号‪你明白吗？
I made that the thing that would end it, you know?
‪我知道 我不想让你嫉妒
I know, I wanted to stop you feeling jealous,
‪所以我不再告诉你那些事
so I stopped telling you things.
‪我很怕在我告诉你 我不想你走之前
I was so scared you were gonna get on that plane...
‪你就上飞机了
before I could tell you that I really didn't want you to go.
‪我想我离开是因为马可
I thought I was leaving because of Marco.
‪我不介意你吻了他
I don't care that you kissed him,
‪但我需要你告诉我…
but I need you to tell me...
‪你爱他吗？
do you love him?
‪请记住我要说的话 好吗？
Please try to remember what I'm about to say, okay?
‪是你 诺亚
It's you, Noah.
‪一直都是你
It's always been you.
‪（你确定要全部删除？）
‪（是的 删除）
‪那么 五年后我想成为怎样的人？
So, what do I want to be in five years?
‪嗯 必须老实说
Well, to be perfectly honest,
‪我一点也不知道
I haven't the slightest idea.
‪大多数和我同龄的孩子‪不管他们在申请论文中承认与否
Most kids my age, whether they'd admit it in a college essay or not,
‪都还在努力想明白
are still trying to figure that out.
‪可能是因为 这不是关于‪我想成为什么人
And maybe it's because it's less about what I want to be
‪更多是我想做什么人
and more about who I want to be.
‪因为我可以告诉你
Because I can tell you this:
‪五年后 我想为弟弟带来快乐
In five years, I want to be my brother's joy.
‪我想是我爸爸的挚爱
I want to be my dad's love...
‪和我妈妈的温暖
And my mom's warmth.
‪五年后 我想能和瑞秋和睦相处
In five years, I want to be Rachel's kindness.
‪我想我是下一位
I guess I'm next.
‪我想有诺亚的勇气
I want to be Noah's courage...
‪我要告诉你 我爱你
I'm telling you that I love you.
‪还有他妈妈的智慧
And his mom's wisdom.
‪但最重要的
But most of all...
‪我想和好友一起欢笑
I wanna be my best friend's laughter.
‪这些加起来 我希望五年后‪能成为这样的人
All those things together is who I wanna be in five years.
‪所以 在这个良辰吉日
And so, on this auspicious day,
‪我最后引用一句名言
I leave you now with one final quote.
‪“我喜欢看到年轻女孩走出去‪抓住世界的衣领
"I love to see a young girl go out and grab the world by the lapels."
‪生活很不堪
Life's a bitch.
‪你必须勇敢 披荆斩棘”
"You have to go out and kick ass!"
‪玛雅·安吉罗
Maya Angelou.
‪这些都是我五年后想要做到的
All of those things is who I want to be in five years.
‪除此之外
And anything else beyond that,
‪可能要等我知道去什么学校‪才能搞清楚
well, I might have to wait until I get where I'm going to figure that out.
‪噢 你收到伯克利的信吗？
Oh, so have you heard from Berkeley yet?
‪ -是的‪ -然后呢？
- Yeah. - And?
‪不 李尔先说
No, Lee first.
‪ -我被录取了‪ -天啊
- I got in! - Oh, my God!
不敢想象
I have no idea.
‪做得好 我知道你会的
That's my boy! I knew you would!
‪ -太好了 兄弟‪ -怎么了？
- All right, bro. - What's up?
‪那你呢？
So? What about you?
‪我…
I, uh...
I...
‪我被列入候补名单了 到处都是
I got wait-listed. Everywhere.
‪伯克利
Berkeley
‪还有哈佛
and Harvard.
‪真可惜 罗谢尔
I'm sorry, Rochelle.
‪谢谢 宝贝
Thanks, babe.
‪我们走吧
‪ -来吧 兄弟 她不值得‪ -我相信其中一个会成功的
- Come on, bro. She's not worth it. - I'm sure one of them will pan out.
‪我知道 你说得对
No, I know. You're right.
‪ -迟点见‪ -迟点 兄弟 我们走吧
See you later.
‪ -别担心‪ -嗯
- Don't worry. - Yeah.
‪她值得的
Yes, she is.
‪我们现在暂时别想了
Ooh! Let's just forget about that right now.
‪我想去玩
I wanna do something fun.
‪你想做什么？
What do you want to do?
我
I...
我喜欢她穿的五颜六色的衣服I love the colorful clothes she wears
和阳光照在她头发上的样子
And the way the sunlight Plays upon her hair
‪ -追上他们‪ -好的
- Okay. - Get 'em!
我听到温柔的话语
I hear the sound of a gentle word
她的芬芳在空中飘散……
On the wind that lifts her perfume Through the air...
‪噢 嘿 想比赛吗？
Oh, hey! You want to race?
‪哦 准备吃灰吧
Oh, get ready to eat my dust!
感觉真好 她给了我...
Good vibrations, she's giving me...
‪我离完美
‪还有无所不知还很远
I'm far from perfect and a long way from knowing everything.
‪但我非常清楚 我想成为我的挚爱
But I do know enough to want to be the very best parts
‪他们人生中最好的部分
of the people I love best.
‪我希望某天 我能做到
I only hope that someday I will be.
我有了好心情
I'm picking up good vibrations
她给了我鼓励
She's giving me excitations
感觉真好 感觉真好
Good, good, good, good vibrations
‪（你被加州大学伯克利分校录取了）
她给了我鼓励
She's giving me excitations
‪（你的哈佛大学入学申请已获批准）
‪噢 天啊
Oh, boy.
我有了好心情
I'm picking up good vibrations
‪好的 记住 这次让我来 好吗？不要说笑话
Okay, remember, leave it to me this time, all right? And no jokes.
‪好的 没问题 老板
Okay. You got it, boss.
-哦 见鬼！-是啊！
- Oh, shit! - Yeah!
‪你能把腌黄瓜放到我嘴边吗？
Can you move that pickle to my bite?
‪你脸上都是划痕 有点模糊
You got scratches all over your face, and you're kind of blurry.
‪嘿 等等
Hey, wait a minute.
‪请稍等 我需要时间拿腌黄瓜
Let's hold on so I can take the time to move a pickle.
‪噢…该死
Shoot!
你知道...
You got it all...
‪ -开始了‪ -噢
You got it.
时间流逝 从不放慢脚步 也不三思后行……
Speeding through time never slowing down Or thinking twice...
‪天啊
Oh, my God.
‪噢 新等级
Oh, new level.
‪噢 该死 这是公斤 对吗？
Oh, damn! These are kilograms, right?
‪该死 美女
Damn, girl.
不知何故 某天 某天
Somehow, someday Somehow, someday...
我的脖子！
My neck!
‪该死
Whoo! Daddy!
‪天啊
Oh, Lord!
‪今年你选择的接吻阵容
Who you've selected for this year's kissing lineup.
‪抱歉 我说错了
Sorry, I up that line.
‪ -天啊 我喜欢她的声音‪ -听起来…很阳光
God, I love her voice.Sounds like sunshine.
‪我看到在你的衬衣里
I can see right in your shirt.
‪抱歉 话说 我是个笨蛋 我把台词说错了
I'm sorry, by the way, for being an idiot, getting my line wrong.
让我们重新开始
Let's start again.
做你的亲吻亭
doing your kissing booth.
‪有音乐吗？
Is there music?
‪是的 是我 我在播幻灯片
Yeah, yeah. It's me. I'm playing a slideshow.
‪只是酝酿情绪 抱歉 各位
Just gettin' in my emotions part of me, everybody.
‪我的罗斯阿姨刚刚… 被巴士撞到
My Aunt Rose was just hit by a bus.
‪ -不会吧‪ -在一个…赌博之旅…在德国
No. On a gambling trip in Germany.
‪ -打中你了‪ -请大发慈悲 不要
I have you... have mercy. Have mercy! No!
‪不是吧 爸爸 什么…？天啊‪我在学校的时候你总是这样
Come on, Dad. Like, what the...
‪该死
God! You always do this when I'm in school. Shit!
‪好的 我们从这里… 开始？
Okay, we'll take it from here?
‪你是很慢地在说话吗？
Are you speaking really slowly?
‪你好 镜头
Hello, camera.
‪你们唱得很棒 幸好马可有空 对吗？
You guys sound amazing. Lucky, Marco was available, huh?
‪是的 我还很惊讶
Yeah, I was actually really surprised when he called yesterday
‪昨天他打电话来问‪说能不能和我们合作
to ask if he could play with us.
‪你的裤子在往下掉
‪这很荒谬
Yeah, it's literally falling off. It's actually ridiculous.
‪ -布拉德 该洗澡了 兄弟‪ -我两天前洗过了
Uh, Brad. It's time for a shower, bud.
‪我就要飞跃斜坡了
But I showered two days ago. And I'm about to do the ramp jump.
‪你这辈子都没能跳过那个斜坡
You have literally never made that ramp jump in your life.
‪嘿
Hey!
‪这是约翰·特拉沃尔塔
It's the John Travolta.
‪不是吧
No way...
‪她会给你第二次机会的 兄弟
she's gonna give you a second chance, bae.
祝你好运
Good luck.
‪但是 在自由式…
‪但是 在…天啊
But in freestyle... but in... oh, my God.
‪是“但是在自由式”
- But in... freestyle. - Freestyle.
今天就不同了
Today's the difference.
‪兄弟 那只鸟飞了…马上
Dude, that broke his right off.
‪天啊
Oh, my God. It literally worked.
‪你好 那边的人 我是李尔·弗林
- Hello, there. Uh, I'm Lee Flynn. - And I'm Elle Evans.
‪ -我是艾莉·依云丝‪ -我们是主持人
‪游戏开始
- We are your hosts of... - Game On!
‪这太烂了
I called that shit.
‪这很傻
This is stupid.
‪所有事都很傻
Everything is stupid.
年刊
Yearbook!
‪抱歉 我没感到尴尬
I'm sorry. I'd like to take that again,
‪我想再拍一遍 因为我多做了动作
'cause I smacked an extra.
‪马可什么时候到？
So when will Marco be getting here?
‪马可已经不参加展位了
Marco's actually not working with us anymore.
‪小薇 那不是… 现在就在你头顶
‪看她做了什么
Babes, that was not... It's on your head now. What's she done?
‪轮到我说 抱歉
It's my line. I'm sorry.
‪他是最棒的男朋友 我要… 嫁给他
- He's, like, the most cool person ever. - Wouldn't marry me.
‪我以为我们…
I thought we were... shit!
‪嘿 为什么我从未试过‪戴太阳镜去学校？
Hey, how come I never wear sunglasses to school?
‪我不知道 因为我们开敞篷车
I don't know. 'Cause we drive a convertible.